Encoded by hunter
crazy4tv. Com
[ announcer ]
Futurama is brought to you by...
Glagnar's human rinds.
It's a buncha muncha cruncha
humans!
[ Loud crunch ]
[ Grunting with effort ]
[ Opener grinds loudly ]
[ Squeaking and panting ]
Ooh!
[ Snuffling ]
[ Ravenous gobbling ]
Aw, somebody likes snouts.
Is it me?
[ Humming ]
Oh, my head!
My precious head!
Oh!
[ Gasping ]
Stupid can opener!
You killed my father
and now you've come back for me!
You all right, bender?
Uh, yeah, I guess so.
But I don't see why
we keep this ticking
time bomb around
just for that dumb animal!
Don't yell at nibbler like that.
You hurt his feelings.
Come on, pet him and make up.
No!
I said pet him.
I'll pet him.
I'll pet him with both hands!
[ Snarling ]
Ow, my ass!
Get off! Get off!
Are you all right?
Eh, it's nothing a
lawsuit won't cure!
Not you.
[ Nibbler whimpers ]
Oh, poor baby.
Chipped a fang.
[ Kissing sounds ]
Hey, I got a busted ass here!
I don't see anyone kissing it!
All right, I'm coming.
Remember:
Rover gets the pill
and pepper gets the suppository.
Next!
Ow!
[ Groaning ]
Ah, it's just
a simple broken fang.
Nothing serious.
What's that you say
there, doctor?
You're going to have
to put him down?
No, I...
But I...
Terrible shame, that.
Shall I do the honors?
No!
Ow!
[ Grunting ]
You about done?
Next time I'm keeping it.
Well, I believe I have
a replacement fang
for your pet
in the next room.
[ Loud roar ]
[ Groaning ]
[ Screaming ]
Well, uh...
The Jaguar didn't want
to cooperate
but luckily he knocked
one of my teeth out.
Now, then...
Ow!
Hey, what are these rings
in nibbler's fang?
Um, I'm still a little woozy
from a gazelle kick this morning
but if he's anything
like the common tree
the rings might indicate
his age.
[ Chortling ]
Yeah, well, good luck.
It would take some kind
of genius
to count all those rings.
He's five.
Happy birthday, young nibbler.
Aw, look how cuddly
he looks in his new cape.
I'd be cuddly, too,
if someone gave me a new cape.
Who's playing "pin the tail
on the moon maggot"?
Ooh, me! Everyone watch
how good I am!
[ Beeping ]
Yay!
And the crowd goes wild!
What prize do I get, cash?
[ Amy ]
Hey, look
at nibbler!
[ Licking sounds ]
Aw, he's holding a spoon.
He's so talented.
You call that talent?
Gather 'round ol' bender
and get ready for the show
of a lifetime.
[ Whistling
"sweet Georgia brown" ]
Ta‐da!
Oh!
Now, he's wearing a hat!
Come on, let's all
sing "happy birthday."
♪ What day is today ♪
♪ it's nibbler's
birthday ♪
♪ what a day for a birthday ♪
♪ let's all have some cake. ♪
[ Fry ]
♪ and you smell like one, too. ♪
[ Applause ]
Hey!
What about this?
[ Whistling
"sweet Georgia brown" ]
[ Leela ]
Bender
you were supposed
to be cooking for this party.
Fine. We'll have rack
of nibbler.
Just make a simple cake.
And this time if someone's
going to jump out of it
make sure to put them in
after you cook it.
So it's a cake you want, is it?
I'll make you a cake
you'll never forget.
[ Evil laughter ]
That'll take care
of those annoying rats.
Now, to make a cake so delicious
they'll have no choice
but to love and worship me.
[ Whistling
"sweet Georgia brown" ]
[ Whirring ]
[ Humming ]
[ Bell ringing ]
There!
This will teach
those filthy bastards
who's lovable.
Now, all I have to do
is spell check it
and it's ready
for my admiring public.
No! Get away from there.
[ Slurping ]
[ Loud chomping ]
[ Angry moaning ]
[ Burping ]
That's it!
Happy birthday!
[ Flushing ]
Bender, what's going...
[ Gasping ]
[ Gurgling ]
No!
Hey, can't you see
I'm using the toilet?
[ Sobbing ]
Bender, how could
you flush nibbler
down the toilet?
Well, step one, I had
to lift the seat.
That was the first
little annoyance.
Am I right, men?
Aren't you upset at all?
How would you feel if I
flushed fry down the toilet?
Only one way to find out.
You have no sympathy
for anyone else's feelings.
Of course I do.
Right now, I feel sorry for you.
You do?
Yeah. I mean
one cantaloupe‐sized
bloodshot eye.
You ain't winning no
beauty pageants, lady.
[ Crying ]
And so we say "good‐bye"
to our beloved pet, nibbler
who's gone to a place where
i, too, hope one day to go‐‐
the toilet.
[ Sobbing ]
[ Flushing ]
I wouldn't feel so bad
if bender just understood
the pain he caused me.
[ Bender laughs ]
Give it to me
straight, doctor.
Don't sugarcoat it.
Very well.
Your entire family died
when a plane piloted
by your fiancée
crashed into
your uninsured home.
And you have inoperable cancer.
[ Laughing ]
Bet you weren't
expecting that one,
calculon!
It's like he doesn't
understand simple
humanoid emotion.
I wish just once
bender could feel
exactly what I feel.
Actually, through
the miracle of science
that can be arranged.
Uh‐oh. Is this going
to be another crazy experiment
that crosses a line
man was not meant
to cross?
[ Woman ]
The official death toll
in that tragic rocket crash
has now been raised to 54,000.
[ Snickering ]
[ Shouting ]
Hey, what the hell
are you doing with my head?
I need to tinker in it.
Why don't you just use
a potted plant like fry?
Quiet you.
I'm installing
an "empathy chip."
And that'll allow bender
to feel other people's emotions?
Yes... if by "allow"
you mean "force."
Ow... ooh...
Son of a...
Oh, dear!
Oh, my! Uh‐oh!
Once more.
Steady now!
There we go.
Now, I'll simply tune it
to Leela's emotional frequency.
My god!
I'm overcome with... feelings.
I'm experiencing
a powerful yearning to...
To cram my gullet
full of mackerel heads.
That's me, baby.
Hmm...
Now I'm worried that
I'm not as smart as Leela.
But at the same time
I feel relieved
that I'm cuter than her.
Uh, that's me.
[ Whispering ]
Thanks for covering.
This time I miss nibbler
and I'm feeling nosy
and opinionated.
Bingo!
That's Leela.
Thank you, professor.
I'm happy bender
can finally feel my pain.
Happy...
I like this feeling.
Just don't revert
to your usual mopey self.
I'm not mopey.
You shut up.
Anger, huh?
How dare you make me feel anger
you one‐eyed jerk
with a dead pet!
[ Laughing ]
[ Sobbing ]
[ Crowd chattering happily ]
Thanks for taking me out, Amy.
I feel slightly
less miserable already.
Hey, you know what
would cheer you up?
You should get yourself a puppy.
A puppy?
[ Sniffling ]
Nibbler loved to eat puppies.
[ Crying ]
What's your problem?
I miss nibbler.
You do?
Hell, no!
It's Leela's stupid feelings.
Why can't she just
drink herself happy
like a normal person?
[ Crying ]
[ Guzzling ]
[ Jealous growl ]
Uh‐oh, jealousy.
You think you're so hot!
Wha...?!
The only reason
you get all the guys
is because you dress
like a tramp.
They're just responding
to my personality.
Uh, Leela, Armando and I
are going to the backseat
of his car for coffee.
You going to be all right
here by yourself?
Sure. I'm having
a great time.
Really‐‐ you two
go enjoy yourselves.
I'm so lonely.
I'm going to go eat
a bucket of ice cream.
[ Crying ]
The spoon's in the foot powder.
[ Sniffling ]
[ Bender groans ]
I'm at the end of my rope.
I can't live another minute
without poor, sweet nibbler.
Too bad he wasn't an alligator.
You know,
when you flush those things
they stay alive in the sewers.
Really?
Yep.
My friend's cousin's
caseworker saw one once.
It's a widely believed fact.
Hmm, sewers.
Thinking, thinking, thinking.
[ Bell rings ]
Hang on, nibbler!
Uncle bender's coming
to save you.
[ Flushing ]
Damn, it's too small.
What do those humans design
this for, anyway?
Aha! Bender, one. Toilet, zero.
[ Flushing ]
See you on the other side.
[ Gurgling ]
[ Knocking on door ]
Bender? Bender?!
Have you seen my sombrero?
[ Gasps ]
Now he's flushed
himself down
the toilet?
Who's he going to flush next?
Hey, it's your fault.
He only flushed himself
because your emotions
made him feel bad.
You're right.
I feel terrible.
Oh, great.
Now you're making
him feel worse.
I guess we'd better
go down into the sewers
and look for him.
Are you crazy?
There's mutants down there.
They'll eat you alive.
They're hideous!
[ Screaming ]
There's no such thing
as mutants.
That's a ridiculous urban myth.
Oh, don't be so sure.
Many scientists believe
humans really could
mutate down there
due to exposure to toxic waste
and radioactive runoff
and good old American feces.
God bless America.
Phew!
Ladies first.
[ Yelling ]
[ Splash ]
[ Fry sputtering ]
Ugh! And the aftertaste.
[ Screams ]
What is it?
I burned my finger.
Okay, check the guidebook.
Looks like we're
under park Avenue.
Ooh, ritzy.
Just think, all this
was probably once
a charity luncheon for the met.
[ Clanking ]
Wait, what's that?
[ Groaning ]
I never should have
thrown out the manual.
Bender, you didn't have
to come down here.
I know, but I just
missed nibbler so much.
[ Sobbing ]
He was so cute.
He was so sweet.
Yuck. This emotional display
is making me nauseous.
Or maybe it's whatever that is.
Nibbler?
It's no use.
We'd better turn back.
Which way, fry?
Hmm. According to this map,
the only way out is through...
That pipe.
Don't worry, it gets wider
after about a mile.
Idiot.
Okay, okay, never mind.
I'll just ask those people
for directions.
[ Muttering ]
Mutants!
[ Screams ]
[ Beeping ]
[ Screaming ]
[ Leela ]
Mutants!
They're real.
[ Screaming ]
I'll take care of this.
Back. Back.
Thanks, handsome.
Please, do not be frightened.
We're harmless.
I have three arms.
I said harmless, not armless.
Lay off him.
You know he's only got one ear.
Hey, aren't you supposed
to be eating our brains?
You're mutants.
Mutants?
Perhaps it is you
who are the mutants.
Please, Dwayne.
Have you looked
in a mirror lately?
Welcome to our village.
It may not be Paris,
but it has a certain...
Quaint charm that I, for one,
wouldn't trade for the world.
You guys realize you live
in a sewer, right?
Perhaps.
But perhaps your civilization
is merely the sewer
of an even greater
society above you.
No, we're on the top.
Daylight and everything.
Oh.
It must be wonderful.
Eh.
Listen, we actually
came down here
to find our pet, nibbler.
He got flushed down the toilet.
Well, if he got flushed
down the toilet
he probably came through here.
Everything always does.
Follow me.
All that is ours
was once flushed down
your toilets.
Over there is our aquarium.
This is our library.
Nothing but crumpled porno
and ayn rand.
And over here is our church.
Wow, you guys worship
an unexploded nuclear bomb?
Yeah, but nobody's
that observant.
It's mainly a Christmas
and easter thing.
Nibbler?
Come to daddy, sweetie‐ookums.
So, is it true that alligators
flushed down the toilet
survive down here?
No. That's just
an urban legend.
Then what are those?
Crocodiles.
We keep them as pets.
Then, when they grow too large
we flush them down
into the sub‐sewer.
Some say there's a freakish
race of sub‐mutants down there.
Please, that's just
a sub‐urban legend.
Oh? Then I suppose you also
don't believe in...
El chupanibre.
[ All gasping ]
El chupanibre? What's that?
[ Guitar strumming ]
Gather 'round, children
for the legend of El chupanibre.
♪ He creeps and crawls
in the midnight hush ♪
♪ silent as a low‐flow
toilet flush ♪
♪ watch your step,
'cause sooner or later ♪
♪ he'll eat you whole
and half your alligator. ♪
Crocodile.
Whatever.
[ Snorts ]
Wait, our pet nibbler
loves fresh crocodile.
It's his favorite treat.
He must be El chupanibre.
Hey, yeah.
You unleashed the dreaded
El chupanibre upon us?
Then you are our sworn enemies.
[ All shouting ]
You don't understand.
He would never hurt people.
Let us help you capture him.
Impossible.
If the legend is true
our only hope is to offer
him a snack‐rifice.
Yes, an unspoiled virgin.
I volunteer.
Nice try, Leela
but we've all seen
zapp brannigan's web page.
[ Laughing ]
Oh, I made myself feel bad.
She'll have to do.
Chain her to the post.
And rip her shirt a little.
Behold. When El chupanibre
comes for the... "Virgin"
he will be snared
by this rope trap.
Shh.
El chupanibre comes soon.
It is nightfall.
Nightfall?
How can you tell down here?
[ Splashing ]
The tide is coming in.
Quiet. The beast approaches.
[ Footsteps ]
[ All yelling ]
[ Gasps ]
Nibbler!
Ah, come here, precious.
Look, everyone,
it's El chupanibre.
That's not El chupanibre.
Say what?
That's El chupanibre.
[ Growling ]
[ Screams ]
I'll take care of this.
[ High‐pitched scream ]
Bender, do something.
I'm too scared.
Leela, your "scaredness"
is being transmitted
straight to bender.
If you care about nibbler,
stop caring about him.
I can't.
I love every living creature.
Even me?
As a friend.
Damn.
[ Sobbing ]
Listen to me, Leela.
I'm an expert at not caring.
The secret is to stop
giving a rat's ass
about anyone else
and start thinking of
the things that you want‐‐
that you deserve‐‐
that the world owes you.
Well, I could use
a new tank top.
Bigger! Bigger!
A fashionable tank top,
and designer boots
encrusted with jewels.
Don't stop now.
You'll need some pants
to go with that outfit.
Yeah.
And I could afford it all
if I didn't have to feed
that stupid nibbler.
Bender is back.
I'll save you, nibbler.
Aw.
Bender's going to be killed!
You know what else I could use?
A weekend at one
of those fancy spas.
And a toblerone.
Huh?
[ Flushing ]
[ Roaring ]
[ Gurgling ]
Yay! You did it!
[ Cheering ]
Let's have a tissue tape parade.
[ Bender ]
No, thanks.
[ Splash ]
[ Whimpering ]
Gather 'round, children,
to hear the legend of bender.
♪ He came from above with... ♪
It's going to be many a year
before someone flushes another
guitar string.
That was a disgusting story.
And it's all thanks to bender.
I love you, bender.
I love you, too.
Get that stupid chip out of me
before I kill myself.
Bender, you won't believe this
but the empathy chip burned out.
The emotion you felt for nibbler
was actually your own.
Huh. Looks like bender learned
an important lesson
about respecting other people's
feelings after all.
[ All agreeing ]
No, I'm wrong.
The empathy chip was running
at triple capacity.
And I still barely felt
anything.
Good night, losers.
You know, bender may not
have learned anything from me
but I think I actually learned
something from him.
So long, jerkwads!
So long.