Encoded by hunter
crazy4tv. Com
♪ Call robo‐rooter
when you flush a towel ♪
♪ and we can also help
with an impacted bowel ♪
♪ robo‐rooter. ♪
Mmm... mmm!
Now this is what I call
1,000 years of progress.
A bavarian cream dog
that's also self‐microwaving.
[ Beep, short buzz ]
Aw, geez, let's just pray
I have the energy to get myself
another beer.
[ Beep, whir ]
Ah, what is this?
The middle ages?
[ Groaning ]
[ Slurping ]
Look at you guys...
No offense, fry
but you've become
a fat sack of crap.
Sack!?
And, bender,
your beer belly's so big
your door won't even close
and that doesn't
even make sense.
Come on, we're taking
you pigs to the gym.
The gymnasium?
Excellent, excellent.
For some reason, I'm frisky
as a squid on Tuesday.
[ Clicking ]
[ Weights clanging ]
[ Gasping ]
Hey, who's up
for a nice hot steam?
We crustaceans don't like steam.
I'm going to go work
out with the nautilus.
What up, Dr. Z?
Yo, yo, yo,
whassup? Whassup?
Give up the rock!
Coed steam rooms...
I love the future!
Uh, fry, you're in
the women's steam room.
Ah... futuristic.
Psst. Look what
life was like
before genetic engineering.
Those poor 20th‐century women.
Hey, handsome...
Is there room in there for two?
[ Snorts ]
You wish.
[ Gasping ]
Hey, Leela,
look who's the superstud.
Hmm, somebody must have
turned down the gravity.
I'll fix it for you.
[ Gasping ]
Give me that.
More weight.
Dr. Zoidberg,
what's that jazz
on your head?
Enough with the questions,
more weight!
More!
[ Growling ]
Maybe you could do more reps
with less weight.
[ Roaring ]
[ Screaming ]
Hey, looks like zoidberg's
finally coming out of his shell.
[ Laughs ]
Get it?
He's coming out of...
[ Roaring ]
[ Growling ]
Nice and gentle.
We don't want
any unnecessary stress.
[ Roaring ]
[ Screaming ]
[ Splash ]
[ Baby crying ]
Is there a doctor in the gym?
I'm a doctor!
[ Women screaming ]
[ Splashing ]
[ Babies crying ]
[ Grunting ]
I wonder why Dr. Zoidberg
is acting this way?
Out of all of us, he always
seemed the most normal.
I am normal.
Amy, take off these rubber bands
and I'll show you
how normal I am.
Fool me seven times,
shame on you.
Fool me eight or more
times, shame on me.
Maybe he has a parasite.
Maybe he is a parasite!
It's always so sad
when a friend goes crazy
and you have to have
a big clambake and cook him!
Yee‐ha!
Now, now, this won't do.
Let me just give old
zoidie a sedative.
Ah... much better.
You can take off
these rubber bands now.
I'll do it.
[ All ]
Stop! No!
[ Bender ]
Moron!
Hmm, oh‐ho!
A‐ha!
There's the problem.
Give it to
me straight,
professor.
Is it fin rot?
It's fin rot, isn't it?
Tell me it's not fin rot!
Relax my chitiny chum.
There's no problem.
You're just heavy
with male jelly.
Blecch!
It must be mating season
for zoidberg's people.
A chaotic time
when his behavior is dictated
by the tiny brain in his rump.
Yech!
There's only one thing
we can do...
I'll get the water boiling.
We, by which I mean you
will have to rush him
to his ancient homeworld
which will shortly erupt
in an orgy of invertebrate sex.
Oh, baby, I'm there!
Fry, do you even understand
the word invertebrate?
Nope, but that's not the word
I'm interested in.
No need to pack pants, people!
Let's roll!
Dr. Zoidberg said
I should hold these
while he's gone.
[ Roaring and screaming ]
[ Bender ]
Moron!
Welcome home, old friend.
Just 19 hours
until the mating frenzy.
Excellent, excellent.
See you there, doctor...
[ Squishy gurgling ]
Is that how you say zoidberg?
[ Crying ]
You didn't have
to call attention
to his speech impediment.
You're looking less nuts,
crabby.
I'm feeling less nuts, thank you
because tomorrow, I will
be depositing my jelly
in the cloacal vents of a female
if you catch my drift.
Who's the lucky lobsterina?
I don't know yet
but I shall attract one
this afternoon
with an erotic display.
It's amazing that your people
can fall in love so fast.
Love? That word
is unknown here.
I'm simply looking
for a female swollen with eggs
to accept my genetic material.
You and me both, brother.
Ah, my old scuttling grounds.
Let's pull over.
I used to hang out
here as a larva.
It looked so much
bigger back then.
Who's the tough guy now, Vinnie?
[ Loud chewing ]
[ Snarly gurgling ]
Look, outdoor theater.
Let's get tickets.
Oh, let's do.
No, it's the ceremony
of claw plock
where my species
fight to the death
over matters of honor.
Also whether abbreviations
count in scrabble.
They don't.
I didn't come here
to see any activity
involving two guys.
Where do you people do
your erotic display?
Same place as your species...
The beach.
How do I look?
Like whale barf.
Then the illusion is complete.
Hey, I wonder if
these guys are here
to watch the
erotic display, too.
Perfect. This ought to make me
stand out.
[ Squawking ]
[ All squawking ]
[ Laughs ]
Look how ridiculous they look.
Please, he's no different
from the rest of you organisms
shooting DNA at
each other to
make babies.
I find it offensive.
[ Squawks ]
Keep your jelly
away from my eggs.
[ Squawks hopefully ]
So not interested.
[ Squawks desperately ]
Hmm! I've heard
that line before.
[ Gurgling happily ]
[ Squawking ]
Oh, what's the point?
[ Sighing ]
Why is zoidberg
the only one still alone?
'Cause he's a loser, that's why.
He's the lobster equivalent
of fry.
Hey, I can get
any girl I want,
anytime I want.
I'm just too busy.
[ Gurgles hopefully ]
Edna.
Edna, it's me, zoidberg.
Remember? From high school?
[ Quizzical gurgle ]
You used to laugh at me
because my face was covered
with barnacles?
[ Gasping ]
Zoidberg?
Well, I didn't know
you were back in town.
I heard you went off
and became a rich doctor.
I've performed
a few mercy killings.
So, as long as I'm in town
I was wondering if maybe...
[ Squawks ]
Oh, gee... yeah, I'm...
Just going through a
lot of things right now
and... look, zoidberg
I carry more eggs
than any other female
and I... owe it to our race
to pick a mate
who's stuffed with male jelly.
Maybe a rock star.
Or maybe a doctor.
I'm sorry, zoidberg
you're just
an inferior
male specimen.
Nice seeing you again.
[ Zoidberg ]
No one will ever want
to mate with me.
Not with a puny claw like this.
Did you see those other guys?
They look like giant claws
with bodies attached.
At least you didn't
smell as bad as them.
You're right!
My stink gland is weak. Smell.
[ Gagging ]
Listen, doc, if
you want to score
you've got to fake
like you're in love.
Just look her in
the eye, start
crying and say
"I've never been so happy."
Oh... if a guy ever did that
to me, I'd know it.
Wait a second.
They've all been doing that
to me.
Even Sean.
[ Crying ]
Hmm... this "love"
intrigues me.
Teach me to fake it.
Okay, you're on a date.
What's the first thing you do?
Ask her to mate with me.
No. Tell her she's special.
But she's not.
She's merely the female
with the largest clutch of eggs.
Well, tell her that, and then...
Then mating.
No, make up some feelings
and tell her you have them.
Yes?
Is desire to mate a feeling?
Oh, you're not even trying.
[ Gurgles in frustration ]
It's all so complicated
with the flowers and the romance
and the lies upon lies...
Okay, okay, don't worry.
The love‐meister
will take you under his wing.
What, now there's
a bird involved?
Okay, go ahead.
What the..? Dr. Zoidberg?
Your mating display failed.
Why are you trying
to talk to me?
I have no idea.
You just want to talk.
It has nothing to do
with mating.
I just want to talk.
It has nothing to do
with mating.
Fry, that doesn't make sense.
Dr. Zoidberg, that doesn't make
sense... but okay.
Start with a compliment.
Tell her she looks thin.
You seem malnourished.
Are you suffering
from internal parasites?
Why, yes. Thanks for noticing.
Now ask her how her day was.
Why would I want to know?
You wouldn't. Ask anyway.
How was your day?
Well, first, I got up
and had a piece of toast
then I brushed my teeth
then I went to the store
to buy some fish, then I...
Fry, look what you did.
She won't shut up.
That's normal.
Just nod your head and say,
"uh‐huh."
Uh‐huh, uh‐huh.
And then you threw
an octopus at my window.
You know, zoidberg, it's crazy,
but when you talk this way
your obvious deficiencies
as a male seem...
Less obvious.
Your genes seem
less detrimental.
[ Sniffing ]
You even stink more.
Do I ask her to mate now?
Third date.
So I returned
his artificial heart
and ever since then
I've been known by the name
of honest bender.
[ All laughing ]
I'd like to
propose a toast
to... coat check #84.
[ Whispering ]
Turn it over.
Oh. Edna,
of all the slimy,
gross crab monsters
on this planet
you are apparently the hottest.
Oy.
That's the most beautiful thing
I've ever heard.
Yes, well, excuse me.
I've got to powder
my mouth flaps.
[ Groans ]
Uh, me, too.
I'm confused, fry.
I'm feeling a strange
new emotion.
Is it love
when you care about a female
for reasons beyond mating?
Nope. Must be some weird
alien emotion.
Zoidberg said some dumb stuff
but he's a nice guy, really.
It's just that fry's been
telling him what to say
and fry's a... do you have
idiots on your planet?
Fry?
You mean, words of such beauty
came from the blowhole
of that hideous alien?
Yeah. What?
Look, never mind the words.
Zoidberg's a doctor.
A doctor, honey.
Hmm...
[ Buzzes ]
[ Edna ]
Come in.
[ Seductive purring ]
Hello, fry.
Can I interest you
in some surf and turf?
No, thanks.
I just came to tell you
that zoidberg's really great.
He's got male jelly
coming out the wazoo.
Well, that is where it comes out
but jelly isn't everything.
I know zoidberg's
magical words were
really yours.
Teach me to love you
squishy poet
from beyond the stars.
Uh, I'm flattered, really.
If I was going to do it
with a big, freaky mud bug
you'd be way up the list.
Hush, you romantic fool.
Engage your mandibles
and kiss me.
[ Voracious gurgling ]
[ Fry grunting ]
[ Knocking ]
Edna?
I couldn't stand it
any longer. I...
[ Screams ]
[ Wheezing ]
Fry!
Dr. Zoidberg,
it's not how it looks.
Her caviar is on your neck!
But...
Oh, it's true, zoidberg.
We can't hide it any longer.
Fry and I have fallen in love
and we're going
to mate tomorrow.
What?!
Fry, I challenge you
to claw plock.
English, please?
A fight to the death.
And if you survive,
we'll make sweet love.
[ Screams ]
The law is clear.
Fry and zoidberg
shall fight to the death
for the claw
of the beautiful edna!
But I don't want her!
Once invoked, the sacred
tradition of claw plock
cannot be taken back.
It is a recent tradition,
only 18 years old
but it is a tradition
nonetheless!
[ Cheers ]
Get ready, fry.
I'm going to rip
your swim bladder out
and show it to you.
Dr. Zoidberg,
this is madness!
You're being irrational!
Of course I'm being irrational!
I'm in love!
Aw...
Leela!
Right, right.
You have to stop this madness!
Listen, lady,
as you can plainly see
I'm a highly desirable male,
groaning with jelly
yet I embrace a life of celibacy
in order to uphold
our crazy traditions.
One of your friends must die!
Fate is cruel and unyielding,
and what must be, must be.
Taking all bets!
I'm giving nine to two
on zoidberg
the crab with the jab,
the great red hope.
Come on, baby!
Fry, it's been years
since medical school
so remind me: Disemboweling
in your species‐‐
fatal or non‐fatal?
Fatal.
Large bet on myself
in round one!
Edna, have you anything to say
before begins the claw plock?
I do.
I just want to say
that today I got up
and I had a piece of toast.
Then I brushed my teeth...
Shut up!
I love you, fry!
[ Roaring ]
No!
Fry, having guessed what animal
I was thinking of
you shall have
first choice of weapon.
[ Claws clicking ]
[ Fry ]
Uh‐huh... ah!
And you, doctor?
I choose my own claws.
I want the tactile pleasure
of chopping him
right here, in the gonads.
Shh!
Nobody correct him!
Fry, I've never asked you
for anything before
but if it's not too much trouble
when it comes to the ninth round
just let him win.
But it's a fight to the death!
Oh, so suddenly
this is all about you!
Please rise
for the national anthem.
[ Star Trek
battle theme playing ]
Uh‐oh.
Let claw plock begin!
Ow!
[ Laughing ]
[ Chuckling ]
[ Growling ]
[ Screams ]
[ Panting ]
[ Cheering ]
Come on, fry!
Die with dignity!
A‐ha!
Oops.
No! I can't stand to look!
[ Audience gasps ]
[ Groaning ]
Crack him open!
Kill him!
Psst! Fry, take a dive!
[ Crowd chanting ]
Claw plock,
claw plock, claw plock!
[ Crowd gasping ]
My fellow fish monsters,
far be it from me to question
your stupid civilization
or its dumb customs
but is squeezing
each other's brains out
with a giant nutcracker
really going to solve anything?
Dr. Zoidberg is my friend
and though a woman
has come between us
I say
we'll always remain friends.
And do you know why?
One reason.
You bastard!
I'll kill you!
[ Both yelling ]
[ Leela ]
Wait, stop!
Everyone is gone!
Edna?
Honey?
[ Loud squawking ]
[ All gasping ]
Edna!
[ All ]
Ew!
My god!
The frenzy!
Oh, the greatest experience
in life, and I missed it.
[ Crying ]
Oh, I'm sorry, doc.
Ow! Ow!
Ah...
[ Moans ]
The frenzy is over.
How will I ever get rid
of my male jelly now?
I'll lend you this.
Fry!
Hey, hey!
Shoo, get away!
Hey! What's with
the flying jerks?
They come to feast
after the frenzy.
Once my species
passes on its genes, it dies.
You mean you have to choose
between a life without sex
and a gruesome death?
Yes.
Tough call.
Well, it was nice of you
to let me
reattach your arm, fry.
Especially after I made
a complete eel out of myself.
No biggie.
Yes, biggie.
I learned to feel things
I've never felt before‐‐
love, jealousy,
passion for disemboweling.
I owe it all to you.
There. I pronounce the operation
a success.
Hooray!
Yeah!
I may not know from emotions
but when it comes to medicine?
Forget about it.
I don't mean to nitpick,
super‐doc
but do you think maybe
you could take one
more whack at this?
For you, my friend?
Anything.
[ Laser droning ]
[ Fry screaming ]
My legs!
[ Zoidberg ]
All right, all right.
Third time's the charm.
[ Laser droning ]
[ Moist thud ]