Encoded by hunter
crazy4tv. Com
[ Man narrating ]
You're entering the vicinity
of an area adjacent
to a location.
The kind of place where
there might be a monster
or some kind of weird mirror.
These are just examples.
It could also
be something much better.
Prepare to enter...
As per your request, please find
enclosed the last man on earth.
Finally... solitude.
I can read books
for all eternity.
It's not fair.
It's not fair!
Wait. My eyes aren't that bad.
I can still read
the large‐print books.
[ Screams ]
It's not f‐‐
well, lucky I know
how to read braille.
[ Screams ]
Hey, look at that weird mirror.
[ Shuddering ]
Cursed by
his own hubris.
There's a political debate on.
Quick, change the channel.
Hey, that's what fry said
when we turned on the debate.
[ Announcer ]
C‐span9 presents
the thrill of politics.
[ Snoring ]
[ Sighs ]
Wha‐‐ huh?
Look, I know there
are no car chases,
but this is important.
One of these two men will
become president of the world.
What do we care?
We live in the United States.
The United States
is part of the world.
Wow, I have been
gone a long time.
It's time someone
had the courage
to stand up and say
I'm against those things
that everybody hates!
Now, I respect my opponent.
I think he's a good man.
But, quite frankly, I agree
with everything he just said!
These are the candidates?
They sound like clones.
Wait a minute.
They are clones!
Don't let their
identical DNA fool you.
They differ on some key issues.
I say your three‐cent
titanium tax goes too far.
And I say your
three‐cent titanium tax
doesn't go too far enough.
If I were registered to vote,
I'd send these clowns a message
by staying home on election day
and dressing up like a clown!
You're not registered?!
Nope. Not vaccinated, either.
Besides, it's not like one vote
ever made a difference.
That's not true.
The first robot president
won by exactly one vote.
Ah, yes! John Quincy
adding machine.
He struck a chord
with the voters
when he pledged not to
go on a killing spree.
But, like most politicians,
he promised more
than he could deliver.
The point is, one vote
can make a difference.
And even though it won't
I'm still taking you
to get registered.
Yes, that's a capital idea.
Let's all go register.
Professor, when did you become
so obsessed with voting?
The very instant I became old.
Mmm!
The problem with both parties
is that they always
want to give your tax dollars
to the less fortunate.
The less fortunate
get all the breaks.
You know, fry, you could
join a third party, maybe.
Only weirdos and mutants
join third parties.
Really? I better keep an eye out
at the next meeting.
What party do you
belong to, bender?
Eh, I'm not allowed to vote.
'Cause you're a robot?
No. Convicted felon.
We favor unreasonably
huge subsidies
to the brain slug planet.
Okay, but what are
the brain slugs
who control you
going to do for the working man?
Attach brain slugs to them.
Sure, you say that now.
So is it true you can make
all kinds of shirts
and ropes out of hemp?
Dave's not here, man.
I also heard hemp
makes great shampoo.
It does? No way!
I got to check out
this brochure.
[ Gulping ]
So, what are you doing
to protect
my constitutional right
to bear doomsday devices?
Well, first off,
we're going to get rid
of that three‐day waiting
period for mad scientists.
Damn straight!
Today, the mad scientist
can't get a doomsday device.
Tomorrow, it's
the mad grad student!
Where will it end?
Amen, brother!
I don't go anywhere
without my mutated anthrax‐‐
for duck huntin'.
Sure, humans are cute
but how else are we supposed
to test cosmetics?
I concur.
Now here's a party
I can get excited about.
Sign me up.
Sorry, not with that attitude.
Okay, then screw it.
Welcome aboard, brother!
‐ all right!
‐ you're out.
[ Fry ]
That was pretty cool.
I think I'm actually starting
to get interested in politics.
‐ [ Beeping ]
‐ [ Theme music plays ]
[ Both snoring ]
And so, with two weeks
left in the campaign,
the question on everyone's mind
is who will be
the next president of earth‐‐
Jack Johnson, or bitter
rival John Jackson?
Two terrific candidates,
huh, morbo?
All humans are vermin
in the eyes of morbo.
[ Laughing ]
In other local news
disaster struck on
saturn's moon of
titan today
when a titanium mine collapsed
trapping 1,000 robot workers.
What? Lord have mercy!
Unless something is done quickly
the trapped robots
will be dead within 300 years.
Sir, what rescue operations
are planned?
The plan is, basically,
to pave over the area
and get on with our lives.
[ Horrified gasp ]
News of the mine's closing
sent titanium prices
skyrocketing.
All right! I'm rich!
What are you talking about?
My body's 40% titanium.
I'm finally richer than
those snooty a. T. M. Machines.
Too bad you can't spend it.
‐ oh, can't I?
‐ no.
Watch me, poor man.
[ Shopkeeper ]
Pleasure doin' business
with you.
[ Bender laughing ]
Game's over, losers!
I have all the money.
Compare your lives to mine
and then kill yourselves.
[ Sniffing ]
Hey, get away! Shoo!
I'll give you $5.00
to not do what you're
thinking about doing.
[ Bender chuckles ]
You just lost $5.00.
Hey, buddy! Little help?
[ Grunting ]
Thank you!
[ All gasping ]
Hello, peasants.
Bender!
What happened to you?
You look different.
Did you get a haircut?
No! I sold my body.
[ Spitting ]
Sold your body?!
Oh, bender,
I've been down that road.
I know it's glamorous
and the parties are great,
but you'll end up spending
every dollar you make
on jewelry and skintight pants.
This is crazy, bender.
How are you going to live
without a body?
[ Raspberry ]
Bodies are for hookers
and fat people.
All I need is a wad
of cash with a head
wrapped around it.
Well, at least now
you can pay off your loan shark.
Yeah, right,
what's he going to do,
break my legs?
[ Laughing ]
Ah, this is the life!
Another Martini, please!
Shaken, not stirred.
[ Bouncing ]
Oh, yeah!
Put it all on black.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa!
[ Grunting ]
21 red.
[ Grunts ]
I beg your pardon‐‐ 33 black.
Yes!
The rich get richer.
[ Grunting ]
Strike!
In your face, Leela!
[ Laughing ]
Ow!
[ Screeching ]
[ Screaming ]
[ Muttering ]
[ Grunting ]
Timber!
Hey, bender, can I take
a ride in your car?
Maybe if you clean up first.
It looks like your neck
stepped in something.
Oh, I'm sorry.
That's just your body.
[ Laughing ]
Hey, you look me
in the shins and say that.
Hey, I've had it
up to here with this place.
I'm off to the head museum
to hang out
with classy heads like me
who appreciate the finer things:
Poetry, philosophy, hats.
So long, coffin‐stuffers!
[ Engine revving ]
[ Tires squealing ]
[ Head muttering ]
Could one of you coffin‐stuffers
please carry me?
Now, which group of heads
is good enough for me
to hang out with?
What do you think, fry?
Fry?
Mmm.
Hi.
I'm Claudia schiffer's head.
I recognize you.
Didn't you use to have
a body of some sort?
Yeah, but it was
holding me back.
You know, I just did the cover
of the sports
illustrated
swim cap issue.
[ Purring ]
Well, you're looking great.
Thanks. I wouldn't
mind losing a
few pounds, though.
Couldn't hurt.
Ah, u. S. Presidents!
Sturdy shelves, good security...
This place has class.
[ Clinton ]
Hey, sugar cookie!
You know, legally
nothing I can do
counts as sex anymore.
I apologize
for his rudeness, ma'am.
He gets this way
around meaty‐looking women.
Hey, I remember you.
I was going to vote
for you one time.
But voting isn't cool
so I stayed home alone
and got trashed on listerine.
Frankly, I've never felt voting
to be all that essential
to the process.
No kidding, Ford.
So then the hooker‐bot says
"that's not
my expansion slot."
And my friend says
"that's not my gold‐plated
25‐pin connector."
[ Laughing ]
Oh, bender.
Thou robots really
cracketh me up.
You know, I like it here.
What's the rent
on one of these jars?
Sorry, bender,
but we can't allow
every Tom, dick
and Harry to move in.
No offense Jefferson,
Nixon and Truman.
Maybe Mr. Bender can get a spot
in the closet
of presidential losers.
Bob dole needs company.
Larouche won't stop
with the knock‐knock jokes.
Pass.
So telleth, bender‐‐
what hath happened to your body?
I hocked it.
Hocked it?
Why wouldst
thou do that?
Same reason
you hocked your teeth.
Ah, booze money.
I remember my body.
Flabby, pasty‐skinned,
riddled with phlebitis.
A good republican body.
God, I loved it.
I hear that.
I spent most
of my teen years
loving my body.
Course, it was tough love‐‐
[ grunting ]
Fry, he opened up
relations with China.
He doesn't want to hear
about your ding‐dong.
So, Nixon,
even if you miss your body
being a head's great,
too, right?
No, son.
It's a sad and lonely life.
Oh, great.
Now you tell me.
That's my style.
I like to kick 'em
when they're down.
[ Muttering ]
[ Groaning ]
One, zero, uh‐‐
one, one, zero, zero, one‐‐
[ screaming ]
Bender, what is it?
Whoa, what an awful dream.
Ones and zeros everywhere.
[ Shuddering ]
And I thought I saw a two.
It was just a dream, bender.
There's no such thing as two.
I know what this is about.
My body loved me
and I turned its back on it.
Well, old friend, tie
a yellow ribbon 'round your neck
'cause I'm a‐comin' home.
You sold my body?!
To who?!
I can't reveal that information
but you look like a nice robot.
Tell you what‐‐
I'll give you 50
bucks for the kid.
Hey, my clothes
are worth 50 bucks.
Deal.
[ Moaning ]
How could I let this happen?
I can't go through
the rest of my life like this.
Don't you have
a self‐destruct button?
Yeah...
But it's on my body.
What am I going to do?
[ Sobbing ]
Uh, I can't stand
to see a robot cry.
Let's watch TV.
And so, ladies and gentlemen
I'm throwing my head
into the ring.
I'm announcing my candidacy
for the presidency of earth.
[ Reporters shouting ]
Scoop Chang, Beijing bugle.
Sir, the constitution
clearly states
that nobody can be elected
president more than twice.
That's right... no body.
But as you can plainly see,
I've got a shiny new body.
[ Humming melody ]
[ Gasping ]
Bender, he's got your body!
That dirty,
double‐crossing bastard!
How dare he run off
with Richard Nixon.
Nixon must have bought your body
from the pawnshop.
Yeah, and that electric guitar.
♪ Remember
what the dormouse said ♪
♪ feed your head... ♪
I'm meeting you halfway,
you stupid hippies.
[ Cheering ]
I am not a crook's head.
Yeah, you are.
You stole my body!
Fry, Leela, you got to help me.
Ordinarily, I'd say
no and lecture you
on how this is your
own fault for being
such an idiot.
But when a robotic
Nixon is on the loose,
we have a duty to take action.
Idiot.
[ Audience murmuring ]
Morbo will now introduce
tonight's candidates.
Puny human number one,
puny human number two,
and morbo's
good friend,
Richard Nixon.
Hello, morbo.
How's the family?
Belligerent and numerous.
Good man.
Nixon's pro‐war and pro‐family.
[ Applause ]
Great. First he steals my body,
now he's touching my stuff.
Come on. We've got
to find some way
to talk to him.
Morbo demands an answer
to the following question:
"If you saw delicious candy
in the hands of a small child
would you seize and consume it?"
Unthinkable!
I wouldn't think of it!
What about you,
Mr. Nixon?
I remind you, you are
under a truth‐o‐scope.
Uh, well, uh...
The question is‐is vague.
You don't say
what kind of candy,
uh, whether anyone
is watching...
[ Mumbles, clears throat ]
At any rate, I certainly
wouldn't harm the child.
[ Beeping ]
You scored big points
tonight, sir.
What are you talking about?
They ate me alive out there.
Yes, but your body
stayed on message
and that message is,
"look at my shiny new body."
The robots ate it up.
You've got real charisma
from the neck down.
Nixon with charisma.
My god!
I can rule the universe!
[ All gasping ]
Give me my body back,
you two‐bit thief!
Now, look here,
you drugged‐out communist,
I paid for this body
and I'd no sooner return it
than I would my little cocker
spaniel dog, checkers.
‐ [ Yelps ] ‐ shut up, damn it!
Please, Mr. Nixon
we're appealing to
your sense of decency.
[ Laughing ]
Very good!
Seriously, though, I'm never
giving back this body.
Now, beat it, before I get
Cambodian on your asses!
[ Bender crying ]
It's hopeless.
We might as well turn in my head
for the five‐cent deposit.
No way.
I'm not letting my best friend
get recycled‐‐
not for five cents,
not for 500 cents.
Leela, I've got a plan.
I've got a better plan.
[ Whispering ]
Why would Nixon stay
at the Watergate?
They give you a discount
if you've been here before.
[ Grunting ]
[ Fry ]
Keep going.
We're right behind you.
Whoa, mama. Get
a room, you two.
[ Man ]
We're in a room!
Well, then, lose some weight.
[ Grunting ]
[ Man snoring ]
[ Exhaling loudly ]
[ Snoring ]
Oh, yeah, you women's libbers
really know how to party.
Psst, there I am.
[ Squeaking ]
[ Snoring continuing ]
Hey, Betty friedan,
send a little of
that lotion my way.
Okay, almost got it.
Steady...
Don't panic.
Ooh.
Uh‐oh.
[ Groaning and yelling ]
Huh? What the‐‐
you shaggy peaceniks
have some nerve.
I'm just here for what's mine.
Don't make me kick your neck.
Bring it on, soup can.
‐ [ Growling ] ‐ [ Gasping ]
[ Both snarling ]
[ Growling, snarling
continuing ]
All right, break it up, you two.
That's it!
You're all going to jail
and don't expect me
to Grant a pardon
like that sissy Ford.
You'll never pardon anybody
because you'll never
get elected president.
The voters of earth aren't
the pea‐brained idiots they were
back in your time.
Oh, no?
Well, listen here, missy.
Computers may be twice as fast
as they were in 1973
but your average voter is
as drunk and stupid as ever.
The only one
who's changed is me.
I've become bitter
and, let's face it‐‐
crazy over the years.
And once I'm swept into office,
I'll sell our children's organs
to zoos for meat
and I'll go into people's houses
at night and wreck up the place.
[ Laughing villainously ]
Well, he lost my vote.
Like one vote
ever made a difference.
Now, if you'll excuse me,
I'm going to inch myself
over to the phone
and call the police.
[ Grunting ]
Not so fast, Nixon!
Are you familiar
with... audio tape?
[ Tape rewinding ]
Uh‐oh, I don't like
where this is heading.
And I'll go
into people's houses at night
and wreck up the place.
[ Laughing villainously ]
My god,
I really sound like that?
I thought my voice had
more of a Clark gable quality.
[ Mechanical whining ]
The jig's up, Nixon.
We'll trade you the tape
for the body.
Oh, expletive deleted.
You've got a deal.
Hey, I've got one last thought.
[ Groaning ]
Ah, it's good to be back
in one piece again...
Except I can't get these
damn bumper stickers off.
The sheer drama of this election
has driven voter turnout
to its highest level in
centuries‐‐ six percent.
Exit polls show evil underdog
Richard Nixon trailing
with an estimated zero votes.
Yes! The system works.
The time is 7:59
and the robot polls
are now opening...
And the robot vote is in.
Nixon has won!
Oh, no!
Get out of town!
Ooh...
Why would robots vote for Nixon
now that he's just a head
in a jar?
I give you the next president
of earth!
[ Crashing thunderously ]
[ Grunts ]
Nixon's back!
[ Cheering ]
I can't believe it.
He won by a single vote.
Well, it ain't my fault.
I'm a non‐voting felon,
thank you.
Well, it's not my fault, either,
'cause I forgot to vote.
Oh, crud, I knew there was
something I meant to do today.
Morbo congratulates
our gargantuan cyborg president.
May death come quickly
to his enemies.
[ Laughing ]
[ Pedestrians screaming ]
[ Growling ]
[ Sputtering ]
Who's kicking who around now?
[ Growling ]
[ Howling ]
Knock, knock.
[ Growling and sputtering ]