Encoded by hunter
crazy4tv. Com
That was the worst
delivery ever.
Yeah. I'm never going
to another planet
called cannibalon.
Me, neither.
Food was good, though.
Oh, great news, everyone.
Shove it. We quit!
In that case,
I'll have to hire a new crew
to go on our company vacation.
Vacation?
All right!
Whoo!
This is great.
I haven't had time off
since I was 21 through 24.
It's just my way of thanking you
for not reporting
my countless violations
of safety and minimum wage laws.
Aw, you.
I've booked us all
on the maiden voyage
of the largest, most luxurious
space cruise ship ever built.
The Titanic.
Looks nice.
Hey, uh, where's my suitcase?
Oh!
As mayor of new New York
it's my pleasure to introduce
the honorary captain
for the Titanic's maiden voyage.
A man who single‐handedly
defeated the retiree people
of the assisted‐living nebula‐‐
zapp brannigan!
[ Applause and cheers ]
Oh, god,
not zapp brannigan.
You know zapp brannigan?
Let's just say
we've crossed paths.
Was that before or after
you slept with him?
She's a beautiful
ship, all right.
Shapely, seductive.
I'm going to fly her brains out.
And now, without further ado
I christen this ship Titanic.
Uh‐huh.
Oof!
[ Applause and cheers ]
Hmm.
Well, well, well,
the lady Leela.
Take notes, kif.
You're about to witness
the subtle waltz
known as seduction.
[ Groaning ]
So, trapped on a ship with me.
What say you and I knock
some very sensual boots?
It's tempting but, uh,
I have a fiancé now.
Uh‐‐ um‐‐ uh‐‐
um‐‐ uh‐‐ well‐‐
uh, him!
Fry, darling,
meet zapp brannigan.
Huh?
[ Grunts ]
How do you do?
Hmm.
[ Crowd cheering ]
[ Ship's horn honks ]
Ah, here's my stateroom.
[ Purring ]
Whoa, where is it?
Come on.
Oh!
Now, hermes
you and your lovely wife,
labarbara
have the suite through there.
And Dr. Zoidberg
your marble tank
is on the other side.
Man, first class seems nice.
It'll seem even nicer
once you've seen your room.
[ Amy ]
Looks like we're on
the fiesta deck.
[ Bell dings ]
‐ [ Bell dings ]
‐ [ Tourists clamoring ]
‐ [ Irish folk music playing ]
‐ [ Bell dings ] ‐ [ Sloshing ]
‐ [ Bell dings ]
‐ [ Men grunting ]
[ Bell dings ]
This is it.
[ Leela sighs ]
Well, at least we get a window.
Well, I'm tired of this
room and everyone in it.
If you'll excuse me, I'm going
to pop over to the casino
for the next 135 hours.
I think I'll go fill up
on bisque at the buffet.
I guess that just leaves you
and your fake fiancé...
All alone on a romantic cruise.
Take it off or
I'll break it off.
Okay!
Captain's inspection.
Mm‐hmm.
[ Beeping ]
[ Laughing ]
I'm betting it all.
[ Onlookers oohing ]
Come on!
Baby needs a new pair of feet!
Snake eyes.
Wait, my cheating unit
malfunctioned.
You got to give me a do‐over.
Sorry, the house limit
is three do‐overs.
Next shooter.
Ah.
Give me your biggest,
strongest, cheapest drink.
You got it.
[ Gasps ]
Allow me to introduce myself.
I'm bender.
Charmed.
I'm the countess de la roca.
I was surprised to
see another robot
staying in first class.
Most of the robots
I meet are laborers.
I assure you, I barely
know the meaning
of the word "labor."
[ Laughing ]
Oh, Mr. Bender.
Please, call me bender.
Oh, well, goodness.
I‐i don't‐‐
[ toilet flushing ]
Kif, I'm feeling
the captain's itch.
I'll get the powder, sir.
No, the itch for adventure.
Prepare to change course.
Sir, this is a leisure cruise.
Our path was set by
the travel agency.
That's for schoolgirls.
Now here's a route
with some chest hair.
But that course leads directly
through a swarm of comets.
Yes, comets.
The icebergs of the sky.
By jackknifing from
one to the next
at breakneck speed
we might just get some
kind of gravity boost...
Or something.
[ Groaning ]
It's time to shove a jalapeño
up this ship's tailpipe.
Divert power from the shields.
Full speed ahead.
Oh, yeah.
[ Gasping ]
Amy! Hello!
Mom! Dad?
What are you doing here?
We were planning
on enjoying
a relaxing vacation
but since you're
here, we'll have to
do some meddling.
We met the nicest boy
in the cabin next to ours.
He's not very ugly.
You should marry him
or at least use him to conceive
a grandchild for us.
There he is at the buffet.
[ Sniffing ]
Uh, he seems really nice, but...
Well, I already have
a boyfriend.
Really? Where is he?
And why isn't he here right now
fathering our grandchild?
Uh‐‐
well, our accommodations
aren't great
but it sure is beautiful
out here.
Yeah. It's pretty romantic.
I mean platonic.
Th‐that sure is
one platonic view.
Fry, just be quiet.
I'm beginning to think
this whole fake fiancé thing
was a terrible, terrible‐‐
[ gasping ]
Hmm
Mmm.
Leela, perhaps this
is an awkward time
***
but if things don't
work out with this
pip‐squeak here
I just want you to know
I'll be there to score
you on the rebound.
[ Brannigan humming ]
Uh, look.
Before you get
any crazy ideas,
that was for zapp.
Well, you got
anything else for him?
All right.
Can we try not
to complicate this?
Mom, dad,
I'd like you to meet fry,
my boyfriend.
Hmm?
Mmm.
Mmm!
[ Fry ]
See you later,
wuv‐ums.
[ Amy giggling ]
It would've been nice
if you'd told me
you were going out with Amy.
I'm not going out with Amy.
It's just to fool her parents.
Hey, you're not jealous,
are you?
What?
No, no, of course not.
Good. 'Cause I consider
my fake relationship with you
a lot more meaningful.
Mind if I freshen up
a bit before we go out?
I was just about to suggest
the same thing.
[ Coy giggle ]
[ Buzz saw whining ]
[ Lusty chuckle ]
[ Mumbling ]
Mmm? Mmm.
[ Laughing ]
Pay dirt.
[ Sighs ]
Lovely, isn't it?
Yeah.
But only 93% as lovely as you.
Oh, bender.
Either that was
a computing error
or you're the most
romantic robot I've ever met.
I don't get it, izac.
That bracelet had a diamond
the size of a raccoon's brain.
Why couldn't I steal it?
It's obvious, Mr. B.
You're in love.
Oh, it's true.
But we're star‐crossed robots.
She, a countess
built with a silver
spoon in her mouth.
And me, just a regular
honest Joe.
Hey, you going to pay for those?
Hell, no.
Security to bar area.
Fellas, please,
I'm in love.
Rough him up.
[ Robots pounding bender ]
Ow, oh, ooh, eh!
What are you doing?
This penniless chump
was stealing drinks, ma'am.
I see.
Here you are, sir.
Keep the change.
You got it.
Oh!
Aha!
[ Mumbling ]
Go, professor!
Lean back more!
[ Groaning ]
Ow!
Come on, hermes
you could out‐limbo
all of these people.
Don't be a dog hot, woman.
You know I can't.
Not after what happened.
[ Event announcer ]
Now limboing for the earth team
hermes Conrad.
You're my hero, hermes!
I'm going to be just like you.
No, boy, stop!
It's too low!
Your backbone can't take it!
I'm just like hermes!
I'm just like‐‐
[ back snapping ]
[ Boy gasping ]
Nooo!
[ Sobbing ]
There, there.
Now you don't have to
limbo if you don't want.
It doesn't make you
any less of a man.
Though it did get me
some action.
I like a man who's flexible.
Your attention, please.
As captain of this vessel
the terrible burden
of naming a limbo contest winner
is mine and mine alone.
Shouldn't you be
steering between
the comets?
And the winner is‐‐
Leela.
But I didn't even limbo.
No matter.
I know from personal experience
how horizontal you can get.
As your reward,
you and that hair pile
are invited to dine
at the captain's table
this evening.
Whoo!
Well, now you know‐‐
I'm not actually rich.
I'm a fraud,
a poor, lazy, sexy fraud.
This isn't even a real bow tie,
it's magnetic.
Bender, I don't care
whether you have money.
I love you for
your artificial intelligence
and your sincerity simulator.
You do?
Really?
[ Computer printer whirring ]
[ Laughing and giggling ]
I like your style, fry.
You remind me of a young me.
Not much younger, mind you.
Perhaps even
a couple of years older.
‐ thank you, sir.
‐ but as a gentleman,
I must warn you‐‐
if you so much as glance
at another woman
I'll be all over Leela
like a fly on a pile
of very seductive manure.
Well, rest assured,
Leela's the only girl for me.
Hey, fry.
Amy.
Leela.
Ah, the family wong.
Our party is complete.
What are we going to do?
Fry can't pretend
to be both our
boyfriends.
Sure, I can.
I learned how to handle
delicate social situations
from a little show
called three's company.
[ Glass chiming ]
I'd like to impose a toast
on the happy couple.
Down the hatch.
Hear, hear.
Now let's have a kiss.
Yes, fry,
plant one on your woman.
Uh, let me think.
♪ Come and knock on our door ♪
♪ na na na na na na ♪
Um, Mr. Roper,
what's the holdup?
Kiss my daughter
already!
Wait. I'm confused.
Now, tell me, fry‐‐
which one of these ladies
are you involved with?
Uh‐‐
♪ na na na na na na ♪
Captain, may I have
a word with you?
No.
It's an emergency, sir.
Come back when it's
a catastrophe.
[ Crashing ]
Oh, very well.
Well, with zapp gone
and my parents still here
I suggest fry give me
a nice convincing kiss.
Ah, now there's
something we
can all enjoy.
Mmm.
Hmm.
Sir, remember
your course
correction?
No.
Well, it's proving
somewhat more suicidal
than we'd initially hoped.
Kif, old friend,
I don't know which
disgusts me more‐‐
your cowardice
or your stupidity.
We'll simply set a new course
for that empty region
over there,
near that
blackish,
hole‐ish thing.
Hey, Leela, why'd you
run off from dinner?
I didn't run off.
I had plenty of time
to finish eating and stroll away
while you were kissing Amy.
Oh, look,
I'm not actually
interested in her
if that's what's bothering you.
Oh, are you sure?
I mean, she has two eyes.
You have two eyes.
I know‐‐ we seem
like a perfect match
but I just don't feel that way
about her.
Nice nebula.
Yeah.
Looks like
everybody's
got somebody...
Except me.
And me.
[ Thudding ]
Ow!
What was that?
Oh, my god.
We're heading
straight into a black hole.
[ Fry ]
Talk about a mood killer.
Don't blame yourself, kif.
We were doomed from the start.
Nothing remains now
but for the captain
to go down with the ship.
Why, that's surprisingly noble
of you, sir.
No. It's noble
of you, kif.
As of now, you're in command.
Congratulations, captain.
[ Sighs ]
[ People screaming ]
Okay, we just have to get
from here to the escape pods.
[ Thudding ]
I'm too young to die.
Come on, before it's too late.
You all go without me.
I'm going to take
one last look around.
You know, for, uh,
stuff to steal.
You're going back
for the countess, aren't you?
All right. I am,
but I don't want
the others to know.
If I don't come back
just say I died
robbing some
old man.
I'll tell him you went out
prying the wedding ring
off his cold, dead finger.
I love you, buddy.
Countess!
Bender!
[ Coughing ]
I fell through the deck!
Are you hurt, my sweet?
No. Luckily, a family
broke my fall.
Just hang on.
I'll take care of that fire.
Bender,
you risked your life to save me.
And I'd do it again.
And perhaps a third time.
But that would be it.
Mmm.
When we kiss, I feel like
I'm standing waist deep
in a pool of cold rising water.
No!
[ Both screaming ]
[ Klaxon sounding ]
Hurry.
The escape pods
should be just ahead.
Faster.
[ Klaxon buzzes ]
[ All gasping ]
[ Groans ]
It won't move...
And the door release
is on the other side.
Then we're dead meat.
No one could squeeze
under there.
No one except a legendary
limbo champion.
Oh, hermes.
[ Back creaking ]
Ooh, it's been a while.
Ah!
This one is for that little kid
who's limboing
up in heaven right now.
[ Groaning ]
[ Cheering ]
That's my man.
All right, baby, limbo.
I still got the moves.
Zoidberg, lower the door
another inch.
Just go on through and hit
the release
you hot dog.
Yes, dear.
[ Cheering ]
That's my man.
Yeah, hermes!
Uh, can somebody help me up?
[ Screaming ]
Well, now what are we
going to do?
Wait a second.
Aren't you a member
of the yacht club?
By god, you're right.
I'm a class‐three yacht.
[ Motor running ]
[ Screaming ]
Thank god there are
plenty of escape pods.
We won't have to dress up
like women and children.
We can't leave yet.
We've got to wait for bender.
The high gravity
must be slowing
down his looting.
Amy.
Mom, dad,
you're alive.
Yeah, but so what?
The important thing is
we found you a new man.
A captain.
Oh, mom, I don't‐‐
hi.
Hello.
I don't feel well.
Look, it's our nebula.
Whenever I see it, I'll
think back to that moment
when we almost‐‐
never mind.
Everyone else is off the ship.
Where in Babylon is bender?
I don't know,
but we can't wait any longer.
Good‐bye, bender.
[ Panting ]
Wait for us!
Something's wrong.
We're two metric tons
overweight.
Well, it's not me.
Look!
I'm slipping, bender.
The pull is too strong.
[ Screams ]
I can't live without you.
If you let go, I let go.
No. You have too much
to live for.
It may hurt for a while
but one day
you'll share
your love again.
After all,
it's shareware.
Don't talk like that.
Tragic romances always
have a happy ending.
[ Echoing ]
Farewell.
Noooo!
She's gone.
But she saved all our lives.
Without her,
we're light enough to get away.
[ Crying ]
Don't cry, bender.
Nobody really knows
what happens in a black hole.
It's possible she's still alive
in another dimension somewhere.
Right, professor.
Oh, yes, absolutely.
Not a chance.
[ Making throat cutting
and choking sounds ]
At least I'll always have
her bracelet.
What do you think it's worth?
It's fake, mon.
[ Bender screaming ]