Encoded by hunter
crazy4tv. Com
horsie to pointy guy six.
[ Groans ]
[ Fry chuckling ]
Check.
Hmm...
Get 'im, boys!
[ Vicious yelling and punching ]
Good move.
[ Farnsworth ]
Good news, everyone.
We have a mission
to further the noble cause
of intergalactic peace.
Nope. Watching cartoons.
Sorry.
[ Crashing ]
What's the mission?
It's a delivery
for the Democratic
order of planets.
Doop? What's that?
It's similar to
the united nations
from your time, fry.
Uh...
Or like the federation
from your Star Trek program.
Oh!
Tonight is the ribbon cutting
for the doop's new headquarters.
What are we delivering?
Something without which
no ribbon‐cutting ceremony
could proceed:
The ceremonial
oversized scissors.
We'll get them there
as quickly as we can.
All right, but don't
run with them.
Wow.
There's a million aliens.
I've never
seen anything
so mind‐blowing.
Ooh! A reception table
with muffins!
[ Female ]
Ladies and gentlemen
welcome
to the ribbon‐cutting ceremony
of the doop's magnificent
new headquarters
a fitting home
for an organization
that has fostered peace
throughout the universe‐‐
even between the insectoids
and the space lizards.
[ Chewing ]
Hmm?
[ Applause ]
So, what's it like
on planet amazonia?
Big rats there.
Me crush with club.
That's so interesting.
Maybe we could get to know
each other over a coffee.
I can think of no better place
for this center of diplomacy
than here in orbit
around the neutral planet.
What are your thoughts
on this momentous occasion,
your neutralness?
I have no strong feelings
one way or the other.
[ Applause ]
I hate these
filthy neutrals, kiff.
With enemies, you know
where they stand
but with neutrals, who knows?
It sickens me.
[ Groans ]
Halt!
Why, Leela
I do believe
we've... met.
He means you guys did it.
If you don't mind,
we're here to deliver
the scissors
for the ribbon cutting.
‐ then you're under arrest.
‐ what for?
How do I know these scissors
aren't part of
some neutral plot?
But they're not even sharp.
Who could I possibly
hurt with them?
The yarn people of nylar four.
[ Speaking alien language ]
So, a plan to assassinate
a weird‐looking
alien with scissors‐‐
how very neutral of you.
What?
That was almost
the perfect crime
but you forgot one thing:
Rock crushes scissors...
But paper covers rock
and scissors cuts paper.
Kiff, we have a conundrum.
[ Groans ]
Search them for paper...
And bring me a rock.
Why?
[ Zapp ]
So beautiful
yet so neutral.
Drag them to the ship.
And now, to cut the ribbon
the legendary doop captain
who just returned
from a triumphant carpet bombing
of Eden seven...
Zapp brannigan!
[ Applause ]
What makes a man turn neutral?
Lust for gold?
Power? Or were
you just born
with a heart full of neutrality?
Um, sir...
You're supposed to be cutting
the ribbon right now.
No matter‐‐
I'll simply cut it from here
with the ship's laser.
Sir, I don't think that's wise.
Kiff, if there's
one thing I don't need
it's your "I don't think
that's wise" attitude.
[ Beeping ]
[ Applause ]
Aah!
[ Screaming ]
Whoopsie‐daisy.
Zapp brannigan
you stand accused
of blowing up doop headquarters.
How do you plead?
Absolutely 99% not guilty.
Then the prosecutor
will call his first witness.
Your honor...
I'm just a simple hyper‐chicken
from a backwoods asteroid,
but if it please the court
I reckon I'll call
the entire jury.
[ All gasping ]
[ All murmuring ]
I'm going to allow this.
Members of the jury
did y'all happen
to catch a gander
at who blew up
that there doop
headquarters?
That's the guy right there.
Right over
there.
Yes, indeed.
And are y'all
going to vote
to convict him?
[ All mumbling
in agreement ]
Oh, yeah.
The jury is instructed
to disregard its own testimony.
Your honor, the
prosecution rests.
[ Clucking ]
The evidence against
zapp brannigan is strong
however, in light
of his years of service
and the incompetence
of this hillbilly prosecutor
I'm afraid I must
dismiss all charges.
[ Crowd murmuring ]
Dismiss all charges?
Your honor,
I know the case is closed
and you've rendered your verdict
but I want to testify.
I'm going to allow this.
Now, Ms. Leela,
on the date in question
were you or were you not
wearing a hoopskirt?
That's a stupid question.
What matters is
zapp brannigan is the sorriest
captain I've ever seen
and I saw the idiot
blow up doop headquarters
with my own eye.
[ Murmuring ]
I'd like to cross‐examine
the witness.
I'm going to allow this.
We've met before, have we not?
Yes.
And on that occasion,
did you have sex with someone?
May I remind you,
you are still under oath.
[ Groans ]
Yes.
Please point out
the person in this courtroom
you had sex with.
Whoo!
And his name is?
Zapp brannigan.
The very same zapp brannigan
who did not blow up
doop headquarters.
I rest my case.
Ladies and gentlemen of the jury
you may begin
your deliberations.
Your honor,
we have reached a verdict.
We find the defendant... guilty.
Whoo!
Zapp brannigan
you are hereby stripped
of your rank as captain
and dismissed from the doop.
[ Gavel bangs ]
[ Sniffling ]
[ Whimpering ]
I'd like to make
one final statement.
Kiff, come here
and hold up the flag.
And wave it a little,
for god's sakes.
My friends, you can take away
a man's title and his uniform
but you can never take away
his integrity or his honor.
Plus,
it was mostly kiff's fault.
What?
Kiff kroker, you are also
stripped of your rank
and dishonorably discharged.
[ Stammering ]
[ Groaning ]
One day a man has everything
and the next day he blows up
a $400 billion space station
and the next day he has nothing.
It makes you think.
No, it doesn't.
Come, kiff.
It's time to begin
our life as civilians.
That's an order, soldier.
[ Introduction to
"everybody's talkin'" playing ]
♪ Everybody's talkin' at me ♪
♪ I don't hear
a word they're saying ♪
♪ only the echoes of my mind ♪
♪ people stop and stare ♪
♪ I can't see their faces ♪
♪ only the shadows ♪
♪ of their eyes ♪
♪ I'm going where the sun
keeps shining... ♪
♪ Through the pouring rain ♪
Hey, bender?
Yeah?
[ Laughing ]
Whoa!
All right...
This is the third hose fight
I've broken up today
and the second one
using actual hoses.
Now, move your lazy asses
and start scrubbing the ship
like I ordered you to.
You don't have to get
so mad, Leela.
Yeah, fry already wiped off
some of the dirt
with his finger.
[ Chuckling ]
[ Doorbell ringing ]
Zapp?
Leela, I didn't know
where else to turn.
You're the only woman
who ever loved me.
I never loved you.
I mean physically.
What do you want?
Just let me work
for a little food.
Perhaps I could paint a fence
or service you sexually
or mop the floors.
You don't know how to do
any of those things.
Kiff might.
Leela, who are you talking to?
Just a broken‐down hobo
who's hit rock bottom
and his commanding officer.
Why, you're that
disgraced starship captain.
Having him on staff
would distract people
from our horrendous
safety record.
Come in!
I'd like everyone to meet
our new employees.
Uh... which ones are new?
The green dude
and the fat man.
Hmm, I could swear
I've never seen
that robot before, either.
I'm bender.
You know, the lovable rascal.
Oh, yes, yes,
my good friend, of course.
Anyway...
Whoever you all are
I have good news.
You'll be making a delivery
to stumbos four
a planet with such high gravity,
you'll most likely be crushed
under the weight
of your own hair.
Enjoy!
So, this Leela
I know she's
a very sensuous woman
but what manner of captain
is she?
She's really strict.
And mean.
I see.
Does she, by any chance,
give the crew members spankings?
No, she just makes us
do work and stuff.
Good, good.
But should she ever institute
some sort of bare‐bottom
spanking policy
let me go in your place.
I won't have my comrades harmed.
Hey, this guy's all right.
Here's to us poor schmoes...
Working for the man.
Even if he is
a hot, sexy, female man.
Mm.
I've computed our landing
coordinates, captain.
Thanks, kiff.
Very nice work.
[ Sighs ]
Wait. What?
I said, "very nice work."
This is the happiest
day of my life.
Mmm!
Okay, crew, listen up.
Your job is to deliver
these 40 pillows to that hotel.
They're not very heavy
but you don't hear me
not complaining.
They're not heavy in here
because we have
an anti‐grav pump
but once you get out
on the surface
the gravity will be
very intense.
Hey, no prob.
This lead apron will protect me.
I don't want any screwups.
Use the hover Dolly
and just deliver
one pillow at a time.
Hey, here's an idea‐‐
let's deliver all
the pillows at once.
‐ yeah.
‐ that's using the old noodle.
[ All grunting ]
Come on, girdle.
Hold.
[ Groaning ]
Uh‐oh.
[ Grunting ]
What the hell happened?
Some breaking occurred.
The Dolly was involved.
That's about all we know.
I told you dumb apes
not to overload it.
Each of those pillows
weighs 150 pounds here.
All right, don't get your
panties in a knot.
We'll just use the backup Dolly.
I'll start loading
up the pillows.
[ Leela ]
No way, Jack.
You disobeyed an order
so now you have to deliver
all 40 pillows by hand.
Let me ask you a serious
question, Leela.
Does the company
that made your bra
make a girdle as well?
I ask because
a friend of mine...
Just get to work.
[ Grunting ]
[ Imitating Leela ]
"I'm Leela. Get to work.
Na, na, na."
I agree.
[ Kiff ]
The point is
it's just so humiliating
working for that man.
Once, he actually ordered me
to shave his armpits
while he was in the bathtub.
So I said to him...
You know, why don't we talk
about something
besides zapp for a while?
Oh, all right.
Um...
Well, how about
them, um... okay.
Well, there he was
in the tub, all right?
[ Sighs ]
[ Grunting ]
[ Thunder rumbling ]
Ah... some good,
old high‐gravity rain.
That'll cool us off.
[ Grunts ]
Ow.
Ow, ow!
[ All grunting and groaning ]
This is all Leela's fault.
Yeah.
If she had let us use
the backup Dolly
we could have broken it
given up, and gone home by now.
You know, boys
a good captain needs many skills
such as boldness, daring
and a velour uniform
and I'm not convinced Leela
has any of those things.
Ah, Leela's not that bad.
I just wish she didn't
make us work so much.
Back when I was captain
all I asked from my men was
their complete loyalty.
If I had that,
then for all I cared
they could sit around
the whole day drinking beer
in their underpants.
Beer?
Underpants?
Ah.
But now, zapp's not
captain anymore.
I'm free!
Oh, you hear that?
I'm actually laughing.
This is a mutiny!
[ Groaning ]
You're out of here, lady.
Zapp's the new captain.
All hail the new captain.
[ Zip ]
Leela, you may be a formidable
doer of the nasty
but I am forced
to relieve you of your post.
On what grounds,
you slobbering oaf?
Failure to prevent a mutiny.
Throw her in the brig.
We don't have a brig.
Then throw her
in the laundry room
which will hereafter
be referred to as the brig.
You really don't want me
to be captain anymore?
You got it, genius.
But didn't I do a good job?
You were mean, and you yelled
and you made us do
all that work.
Sometimes, a captain needs
to do those things.
Besides, I thought
we were friends.
Yeah, well
you shouldn't have been
such a mean captain, then.
Don't worry, Leela.
Soon, we'll be
able to look back
on this and laugh.
[ Cruel laughing ]
Back in my old uniform.
And it nearly still fits
even after all that
fattening hobo cuisine.
What shall I do with
your civilian clothes, sir?
Take them to the laundry brig.
So, do I have your loyalty, men?
To the ends of the universe.
Ten hundred percent.
That's not nearly loyal enough.
I order you to sit around
and drink beer
until you're as loyal
as kiff here.
Yes, sir, sir.
Um, may I have a beer, sir?
No, you're loyal enough already.
Meanwhile, I have a plan.
We will single‐handedly attack
our archenemy,
the neutral planet.
Oh, geez.
Once the neutral
war machine lies in ruins
I'll be a hero again
and the doop will
reinstate me as captain.
But, sir, that plan
makes no sense.
Maybe not to you, kiff.
But if I recall correctly
you were court‐martialed
in disgrace.
Ooh, burn!
Nailed you, buddy.
Prepare to continue
the epic struggle
between good and neutral.
This is awesome.
We're going to be, like,
"pow, pow, pow!"
And they're going to be like,
[ Screams ]
[ Imitating explosions ]
And then, we'll have pancakes
to celebrate
and I'll be, like...
[ Making eating sounds ]
Precisely.
Now, in the name of all
that is good and honorable
we'll call the neutral president
with a message of peace,
then blast him.
Yes, sir, sirdy, sir, sir, sir!
Fly the white flag of war.
This is zapp brannigan
of the good ship...
Planet express ship.
I come swinging
the olive branch of peace.
Should we trust him,
your neutralness?
All I know is,
my gut says, "maybe."
What now, chief?
Now, we crash the ship
into their headquarters
killing them
in a hellish firestorm
from which no living thing
can escape.
Good, good.
Then what?
Then your mission is complete.
I, meanwhile,
will have ejected to safety
wearing the only space suit
on board.
[ Whooping and hollering ]
Wait a second.
Is this plan
going to kill us?
Of course.
What do you think
I meant by loyalty?
Now, help me into
the only space suit.
It looks a bit sweaty in there
so you may need
to apply baby powder.
Leela, we want you
to be captain again.
Let me guess:
He canceled nap time?
He ran out of beer?
So he's about to kill us.
We want Leela
to be captain again.
So, it's mutiny, is it?
I never thought I'd see the day.
Come, kiff, let's eject.
I found a children's space suit
you can wear.
Well, to be honest, sir
I'd rather stay here
with captain Leela.
She actually listens
to what I have to...
[ Muffled speech ]
Oh, no!
He's disabled the steering!
We're gonna crash!
Leela, save me!
And yourself, I guess.
And my banjo!
And fry!
Okay, okay.
We have one chance.
Are you willing to do
what I say as captain?
Absolutely.
Even if I make you work hard?
As your god is my witness.
Then go get the
hover Dolly you
didn't break
and load all the dark matter
into the left engine.
Oh, man, that crap's heavy!
‐ and warm.
‐ just do it!
[ Siren sounding ]
Your neutralness,
it's a beige alert.
If I don't survive
tell my wife, "hello."
Hurry!
I don't want to die
at the age of 25!
Honey, unless we hit a time warp
I wouldn't worry about it.
[ Grunting ]
It's too low!
Quick!
[ Both grunting ]
[ Leela ]
You did it!
You actually did it!
[ Cheering ]
And no one will have to punish
anyone for the mutiny!
And so,
when captain Leela panicked‐‐
perhaps distracted
by female troubles‐‐
my quick thinking allowed me
to do whatever I did
to save the day.
Captain Leela
is this rambling story
of magic and heroism true?
Well, actually...
That‐a‐girl!
If they don't take him back,
we can keep him as captain.
[ Clicks tongue ]
Your honor, it's all true‐‐
my female incompetence,
zapp's catlike reflexes
the stuff that made no sense,
all of it.
[ All gasp ]
[ Chicken squawk ]
In that case, zapp brannigan
I hereby restore your rank
and parking privileges.
[ Satisfied chuckle ]
[ Cheering ]
Oh, foo!
Come, kiff
we've got work to do.
[ Clicks tongue ]
[ Groaning ]
I'll call and tell you about it.
[ Sighs ]
Leela
I just want you
to know that even
though you're mean
you're the best captain ever.
Yeah, you're one dynamite lady.
Can we have the week off?
No!
Please?
Come on, captain.
Oh, all right.
No time off!
Oh, man.
Let's mutiny.