Encoded by hunter
crazy4tv. Com
[ Fry ]
This is awesome!
I've been waiting
a thousand years
to see a beastie boys show.
Can I get anybody a beer?
Sure.
Ah...
[ Man ]
Ladies and gentlemen,
here to lay down
some old, old, incredibly old
school beats, the Beastie Boys!
[ Wheels squeaking ]
♪ Well, now, don't you tell me
to smile ♪
♪ you stick around,
I'll make it worth your while ♪
♪ like numbers beyond
what you can dial ♪
♪ maybe it's because we're
so versatile ♪
♪ "style, profile," I said ♪
♪ it always brings me back
when I hear, "ooh, child" ♪
♪ from the Hudson river... ♪
Impressive.
They're busting mad rhymes
with an 80% success rate.
I believe that qualifies as ill.
At least from a
technical standpoint.
[ Fry ]
Will you guys
shut up?
I'm trying to look cool.
♪ ...for the flintstone flop ♪
♪ flop ♪
♪ Tammy d gets biz
on the crops ♪
♪ crops ♪
♪ Beastie Boys known to let
the beat... mm, drop? ♪
Ow! How's it going?
Ow! Enjoying the show?
Ooh! Ow!
Don't forget to pick up
a t‐shirt.
Wow, an old‐ fashioned mosh pit.
Come on, guys.
Tonight we're going to
party like it's 1999...
Again.
Ow!
Hey, watch it!
[ Karate yell ]
Man, these guys rock
harder than ever.
♪ Oh, my ♪
♪ it's a mirage ♪
♪ telling you
all it's a... ♪
♪ Sabotage ♪
♪ sabotage, yeah. ♪
Peace! We out!
[ Wheels squeaking ]
[ All cheering ]
Hey, bender.
Hey, Fender.
Man, I haven't seen you
since high school.
You still working at
Jack in the box?
Not anymore, baby.
I'm with the band.
Oh‐oh, yeah.
Hey, fellas
I want you to meet my friends
bender, fry, and Leela.
You know, we're really not that
interested in meeting them.
Wow, I love you guys.
Back in the 20th century
I had all five of your albums.
That was a thousand years ago.
Now we got seven.
Cool. Can I borrow
the new ones?
And a couple of blank tapes?
Hey, bender, why don't
we ditch these organ sacks
and hit the real party?
Count me in.
I'm going to drink
till I reboot.
[ Electrical crackling ]
Hey, what kind of party is this?
There's no booze
and only one hooker.
Don't be a drag, man.
We're jacking on.
O‐o‐o‐h, y‐y‐yeah!
Want a jolt?
Uh, hey, I'm no square
but isn't that counter‐indicated
by my operations manual?
[ All laughing ]
Come on, bender.
Grab a Jack.
I told these guys you were cool.
Well, if jacking on will make
strangers think I'm cool
I'll do it.
Whoa!
[ Blubbering ]
[ Psychedelic sitar music
playing ]
[ Swallowing sounds ]
Easy, baby, you
don't want to get
hooked on this stuff.
Ah, no need to worry.
I don't have
an addictive personality.
[ Glass shatters ]
[ Blubbering ]
Hey, uh, bender,
what are we doing
in this bad neighborhood?
Shut up, square!
I'll just be a minute.
[ Whistling ]
Wretched sinner unit
the path to robot heaven
lies here
in the good book 3.0.
Hey, do I preach to you
when you're lying
stoned in the gutter?
No.
So beat it!
Tsk‐tsk‐tsk.
Who was that guy?
Your mama.
Now shut up and drag me to work.
Our electric bill is
climbing faster
than a green snake
up a sugarcane.
Obviously, someone 'round here
been wasting a
whole heap of juice.
Probably you.
Me?
Good morning, bender.
None of your business!
Get off my back!
What's his problem?
If I didn't know better
I'd almost think he
was abusing electricity.
Bender? No way.
[ Electrical crackling ]
I definitely would have
noticed something.
Bender, why are you spending
so much time in the bathroom?
Are you jacking on in there?
No! Don't come in!
Good news, everyone.
Today you'll be delivering
a crate of subpoenas
to sicily eight, the mob planet.
All right, let's get to work!
I'll be out in a second.
I know big Vinnie said
he was giving me
the kiss of death
but I still think he was gay.
Did he use his tongue?
A little.
‐ are you okay, bender?
‐ none of your business!
Get off my back!
Uh‐oh. There seems to be
an electrical disturbance
in the coalsack nebula.
‐ a what kind of a disturbance?
‐ electrical.
Anyway, it's going to take
some careful piloting
to avoid it.
[ Metal creaking ]
[ Crazed laughter ]
We're out of control!
We're heading straight
into the electric field.
[ Fry ]
What's happening?
I feel weird.
Come on, universe!
You big, mostly empty wuss!
Give me all the juice you got!
[ Blubbering ]
Oh, mama.
[ Moaning ]
[ Loud crash ]
What?
[ Leela ]
Bender, we didn't mind
your drinking
or your kleptomania
or your pornography ring.
In fact, that's
why we loved you.
But this electricity abuse
crossed the line.
You almost killed us.
[ Fry ]
And you made me feel
like a jerk for trusting you.
Just like when my friend
Richie swore
he wasn't taking drugs
and then he sold me
my mom's vcr.
And then later, I found out
he was taking drugs.
You make me ashamed
to be your friend.
Oh, you're right.
I'm a lost cause.
[ Pipe organ music playing ]
Maybe there's another way.
Oh, yeah, that's the good stuff.
What am I doing?!
What have I become?!
I see a lot of fancy robots
here today
made of real shiny metal.
But that don't impress
the robot devil, no, sir.
No, sir!
'Cause if you're a sinner
he's going to plug
his infernal modem in the wall
belching smoke and flame,
and he's going to download you
straight to robot hell.
Straight to hell!
So I ask you
who will stand up and be saved?
Who? Who?!
[ Weakly ]
Me.
And as a further
cost‐cutting measure
I have eliminated
the saltwater cooler.
This is a witch hunt.
[ Bender ]
♪ oh, what a beautiful morning ♪
♪ oh, what a beautiful day. ♪
Greetings, friends.
Don't we all look nice today?
Great. He's whacked out
on electricity again.
No, I'm whacked out on life.
My friends, I found religion.
Religion?
Is this another scam
to get free yarmulkes?
Give him a break, fry.
If this helps bender
clean up his act
then I think we should
be supportive.
[ All agreeing ]
Wonderful.
Then you'll all come to my
exceedingly long
un‐air‐conditioned baptism
ceremony.
Um...
Oh, I...
Uh...
We are gathered here today
to deliver brother bender
from the cold, steel grip
of the robot devil
unto the cold, steel bosom
of our congregation.
Tell it, preacher!
That equals true.
Brother bender
do you accept the principles
of robotology
on pain of eternal damnation
in robot hell?
Yes, I do.
Then I will now baptize you.
Press any key to continue.
Uh, while you're at it
could you touch up this seam?
[ Laughing ]
This is unbelievable.
The old bender never would
have taken us out to dinner.
The old bender's gone.
He won't trouble you anymore.
Would monsieur care
to see the wine list?
No poison for us, thanks.
I'll stick with
good old mineral oil.
Ah. Functional.
Mm.
That's mine here.
I'm hungrier than a green snake
in a sugarcane field.
Friends, friends,
surely you're not going to eat
before we say robot grace.
Oh, man.
Uh...
In the name of all that is
good and logical
we give thanks for the chemical
energy we are about to absorb.
To quote the prophet jerematic
[ droning ]
"One‐zero‐zero‐zero
"one‐zero‐one‐zero‐
one‐zero‐one‐zero‐one...
"Zero‐zero‐one...
Zero‐one‐one‐zero‐zero‐one...
Two."
Amen.
Does that mean we can eat now?
Yes.
But first, since I love
you all so much
I'd like to give everyone hugs.
Come here, fry.
Oh, uh, but I don't want to.
[ Contented sigh ]
Fry, you're my friend.
Come on, everyone
line up for a hug.
Let's tear down some
emotional walls.
What are you doing to my ship?
Sanctifying it.
There. That ought to convert
a few tailgaters.
Bender's stupid religion
is driving me nuts.
Amen.
If only he had joined
a mainstream religion
like oprah‐ism or voodoo.
We've got to get
the old bender back.
And I think I know
a way to do it.
We have to reacquaint him
with a little thing
called sleaze.
I can't believe somebody hired
an interstellar spaceship
to deliver a package
to Atlantic city.
What are we delivering, anyway?
Uh... this.
Where are we delivering it to?
Uh... here.
Another job well done.
Now back to the office
for an enjoyable evening
of fasting and repentance.
Whoa, whoa.
Wait, bender.
As long as we're here
why don't we take in
some exotic dancing?
Hey, great idea.
[ Gasps ]
But those girls
don't wear cases.
You can see their bare circuits.
Come on, it'll be fun.
Maybe we could even drink
a little fortified wine.
What?!
Drinking wine is a sin‐‐
even if it is
deliciously fortified.
Hey, bender, look at
that woman's purse.
It's hanging by
a spaghetti strand.
Thou shalt not snatch.
And there's hookerbot 5000.
She's got a heart of solid gold.
Hey, sailing unit.
Stop tempting me!
For once in my life,
I have inner peace.
That's for losers.
Come on, sin your heart out.
Go nuts.
Live a little.
Could you hold my
purse for a minute?
Go for it, bender.
You know you want to.
Well...
[ Disco music playing ]
I'm the greatest!
Looks like we got
the old bender back.
You know it, porkpie.
Except for one thing‐‐
[ beeping ]
You know, as a major
Hollywood director
I'll be holding auditions
tonight for my next movie.
And even though you're all
young and naive
I think you might just
have what it takes.
[ Females giggling ]
[ Knocking on door ]
Hey, I'm trying to score here.
Can't you read the
"do not disturb" sign?
[ Grumbling ]
[ Gasps ]
No! No!
Greetings, bender.
Welcome to robot hell.
[ Metal clanking ]
[ Screaming ]
What in hell happened to bender?
Well, he didn't check out.
The ashtray's still here.
[ Chattering ]
Look, nibbler's caught the scent
of vodka and motor oil.
Go, boy.
Follow that stench.
I'm hallucinating this, right?
No, bender.
Robot hell is quite real.
Here's our brochure.
But I don't belong here.
I don't like things
that are scary and painful.
Sorry, bender.
You agreed to this when
you joined our religion.
If you sin,
you go to robot hell...
For all eternity.
Aw, hell... I mean heck.
It's all right.
You can say that here.
[ Chattering urgently ]
Wait, I remember this place.
They shut it down after
all those people
caught salmonella
from the flume ride.
Look.
It's the symbol
of bender's
old religion.
[ Beeps ]
Unbelievable.
It's an actual,
factual robot hell.
Who would have thought
hell would really exist?
And that it would be
in New Jersey?
Actually...
[ Both yelling ]
We know all your sins, bender
and for each one, we've prepared
an agonizing and ironic
punishment. Gentlemen?
[ Playing up‐tempo beat ]
Aw, crap‐‐ singing.
Mind if I smoke?
♪ Cigars are evil,
you won't miss 'em ♪
♪ we'll find ways
to simulate that smell ♪
♪ what a sorry fella ♪
♪ rolled up and smoked
like a panatela ♪
♪ here on level one
of robot hell ♪
♪ gambling's wrong
and so is cheating ♪
♪ so is forging phony I. O. U. S ♪
♪ let's let lady luck decide ♪
♪ what type
of torture's justified ♪
♪ I'm pit boss here
on level two ♪
Ooh, deep‐fried robot.
♪ Just tell me why? ♪
♪ Please read this
55‐page warrant ♪
♪ there must be robots
worse than I ♪
♪ we checked around,
there really aren't ♪
♪ then please let me explain ♪
♪ my crimes were merely
boyish pranks ♪
♪ you stole from boy scouts,
nuns and banks ♪
♪ aw, don't blame me,
blame my upbringing ♪
♪ please stop sinning
while I'm singing ♪
♪ selling bootleg tapes
is wrong ♪
♪ musicians need that income
to survive ♪
♪ hey, bender, going
to make some noise ♪
♪ with the hard drive scratched
by the Beastie Boys ♪
[ Scratching ]
♪ That's whatcha, whatcha,
whatcha get on level five ♪
[ Fry ]
♪ I don't feel well ♪
[ Leela ]
♪ it's up to us to rescue him ♪
♪ maybe he likes it
here in hell ♪
♪ it's us
who tempted him to sin ♪
♪ maybe he's back
at the motel ♪
♪ come on, fry,
don't be scared ♪
♪ I'm sure at least
one of us will be spared ♪
♪ so just sit back,
enjoy the ride ♪
[ Fry ]
♪ my ass has blisters
from the slide ♪
♪ fencing diamonds,
fixing cockfights ♪
♪ publishing
indecent magazines ♪
♪ you'll pay for every crime ♪
♪ knee‐deep in electric slime ♪
♪ you'll suffer till
the end of time ♪
♪ enduring tortures,
most of which rhyme ♪
♪ trapped forever here
in robot hell. ♪
Of course, that's
just for starters.
[ Fry and Leela screaming ]
[ Both gasping ]
Bender, are you all right?
No. Oh, they're tormenting me
with up‐tempo
singing and dancing.
All right, beelzebot.
What'll it going to take
to get our friend back?
Sorry, but I hold
all the cards here.
There's nothing you can do.
Now if you'll just sign
this fiddle contest waiver...
Wait. What
fiddle contest?
Uh... the fairness in hell act
of 2275
requires me to inform you
that if you can best me
in a fiddle contest,
you win back bender's soul.
As well as a solid gold fiddle.
Wouldn't a solid gold fiddle
weigh hundreds of pounds
and sound crummy?
Well, it's mostly for show.
[ Whispers ]
Do you know how
to play the fiddle?
[ Whispers ]
No, do you?
No, but I used
to play the drums.
They're sort of similar.
What happens if we lose?
You'll only win a smaller
silver fiddle.
Also, I guess I'll
kill one of you...
Him.
We'll do it.
Very well, then.
Beat this.
[ Playing complex
classical music ]
Well, we're boned.
Your turn.
[ Clearing throat ]
[ Discordant screeching ]
Ha!
Time for the drum solo.
[ Falsetto shrieking ]
Run!
Stop them!
They cheated!
[ Machine gun firing ]
[ Choir singing ]
♪ hallelujah ♪
♪ hallelujah, hallelujah... ♪
Hurry, bender.
I could if you dropped
the stupid gold violin.
Oh, sorry.
[ Shrieks ]
[ Cheering ]
Don't worry, guys.
I'll never be too good
or too evil again.
From now on, I'll just be me.
Uh, do you think you could be
just a little less
evil than that?
I don't know.
Do you think you could survive
a 700‐foot fall?
[ Fry ]
Ah, good old bender.