Encoded by hunter
crazy4tv. Com
honey unit, I'm home.
[ Gasps ]
Monique!
Calculon!
[ Beeping ]
Oh, how I wish
I could believe that.
You may be my evil half brother
but there's no law against
murdering the other half.
[ Music tinkling ]
[ Announcer ]
All my circuits
will be right back
after this word from...
Slurm: It's highly addictive.
[ Surf music playing ]
Look. It's slurms McKenzie.
He's the original party worm.
Ooh.
[ Women giggling ]
Whimmy wham‐wham wozzle!
Let's party!
Look at that worm go.
Who says there are
no more heroes?
[ Surf music ]
Hey, dudes,
you could win a chance
to party with me,
slurms McKenzie
at the slurm bottling plant
on planet wormula.
[ Announcer ]
Just look
for the golden bottle cap
inside specially marked
cans of slurm.
[ Gasps ]
I won.
No purchase necessary
unless you wish to enter.
Odds of winning
mathematically insignificant.
I like those odds.
[ Can rattling ]
[ Gasps ]
Rats.
Just another tooth.
Ah...
[ Gulping ]
Aw...
I got to find that
golden bottle cap.
I've never seen anyone
so addicted to slurm.
This is nothing.
Back in high school
I used to drink
a hundred cans
of cola a week.
Right up until my
third heart attack.
[ Groaning ]
Bender,
what's wrong?
I'm sick.
[ Sneezes ]
You poor baby.
Let me check
if you have a fever.
[ Sizzles ]
Ow!
According to bender's
temperature Gauge
which I suggest
you use next time, Leela
he's running a fever of...
900 degrees.
[ Groaning ]
Bender mon, lie yourself down.
You're paying for that.
I'll have a look
but I remind you
I'm an expert on humans,
not robots.
I'm not bender.
I'm fry.
Really? I thought
you were the robot.
Nope, human.
All right, all right,
spare me your life story.
Now, what seems
to be the trouble?
My tummy hurts
and I've been having
this burning
electrical discharge.
Mmm. Don't worry,
you'll be fine.
Oh, boy...
I didn't have the heart
to tell him
it's fin fungus.
He'll be floating
upside down by morning.
Tsk‐tsk‐tsk.
You should try
homeopathic medicine, bender.
Take some zinc.
I'm 40% zinc.
Then take some echinacea
or St. John's wort.
Or a big, fat placebo.
It's all the same crap.
[ Coughs ]
[ Rattling ]
Hey, what's rattling
around in there?
It may well be
the cause of bender's illness
but more importantly,
it's a flimsy pretext
to try out my latest invention.
To the laboratory.
I call this the f‐ray.
It's like an x ray,
only it allows you
to see through anything‐‐
even metal.
Now, the neutrino beam it emits
is a tad dangerous
so you'll need
protective goggles.
[ All ]
Huh?
You may feel
a slight stinging sensation.
All of you.
Aha!
There's the cause
of your illness.
Hey, that's my watch.
I was wondering
where I put that.
Hey! Now I feel
much better.
Thanks, professor
and, amy‐‐
sorry I took your watch.
[ Chuckles ]
[ Coughs ]
Well, I've got to
go take this suit
to the decontaminators.
You two lock up the f‐ray,
and for the love of god
don't let it fall
into the wrong hands.
[ Laughing ]
What shall we point it at first?
I don't know.
Try it on me.
Ow! My sperm.
Wow, neat.
Mind if I try that again?
Huh! Didn't hurt that time.
Oh, mama.
Hold still, sexy lady.
[ Gasps ]
What's wrong?
That's no lady.
[ Man's voice ]
Damn, chico.
One more upgrade
and I'll be more lady
than you can handle.
Why you so stupid, stupid?
Hey, bite my shiny metal ass.
You couldn't afford it, honey.
Man, all this
prolonged exposure to radiation
is making me thirsty.
Ah! If only there
was some way of knowing
which can had the winning
bottle cap inside.
W‐wha‐what?
I didn't hear you.
I was too busy
using this f‐ray
to look inside of things.
Wait a second.
I'm getting an idea.
No. False alarm.
No, yeah, no, yeah, no. Wait.
No, yeah, yeah. No. No. Yes!
[ Wailing ]
Uh‐oh.
Sorry.
Ah, this thing stinks.
We checked 90,000 cans of slurm
and all we won was this junk.
I never want to see
another can of slurm again.
Man, am I thirsty.
Fry, are you all right?
You did it, fry!
You found the
winning bottle cap.
We won!
[ Cheering, choking ]
[ Murmuring ]
Hey.
[ Playing fanfare ]
Ooh. Wow.
Welcome to the planet wormulon.
I'm glermo your gollyrific guide
to the splentacular
slurm factory.
Uh‐huh. Can we have
our free slurm now?
You'll have all the slurm
you can drink later on
when you're partying with my
good friend slurms McKenzie!
All right!
Whimmy wham‐wham wozzle.
Lay some skin on me, dudes.
Wow. The original
party worm.
Are you ready to get down,
get funky with us?
He'd better be.
That's what we pay him for,
right, slurms?
Right!
In fact, slurms has to party
all night, every night
or he's fired.
Rock on.
But before the party
you're all in
for a funderful treat.
A vip tour of the slurm factory.
Enjoy the tour, dudes.
I'm going to go lie down.
Welcome, my friends
to the wondrous world of whimsy
that we like to call
slurm centralized
industrial fabrication unit.
[ Gasps ]
[ Professor ]
Oh, my.
[ Bender ]
Look, flowers,
and a boat.
[ Rhythmic grunting ]
Who are those horrible
orange creatures over there?
Why, those are
the grunka‐lunkas.
They work here in
the slurm factory.
Tell them I hate them.
[ Glermo ]
As we sail down
the river of slurm
you'll see
our mixologists at work.
They take 900
of the finest ingredients
add a touch of childlike delight
and mix it all
with glacial spring water
from our glacial
spring water generator.
Then, last of all,
we add the secret ingredient
that makes slurm
so deliciously addictive.
So what's the secret ingredient?
It's whatever
your imagination wants it to be.
Oh. But what is it, really?
That's not for you to know.
Now, over here,
the grunka‐lunkas
are inducing wumpus berries
to release their flavor
using sensual massage.
Pst. Those berries.
Those are the secret
ingredient, right?
No.
‐ you positive?
‐ yes.
I'm just asking
'cause they look
kind of secret.
Enough!
There will be no
further questions.
Why?
Hey, look.
The disgusting little men
are starting to sing.
♪ Grunka lunka
dunkity doo ♪
♪ we've got a friendly
warning for you ♪
♪ grunka lunka
dunkity dasis ♪
♪ the secret of slurm's
on a need‐to‐know basis ♪
♪ asking questions in school ♪
♪ is a great way to learn ♪
♪ if you try that stuff here
you might get your legs broke ♪
♪ we once found a dead guy
face‐down in the slurm ♪
♪ it could easily happen
again to you folks ♪
♪ so keep your head down
and keep your mouth shut ♪
♪ grunka lunka lunka
dunkity dutt! ♪
Hey! I don't pay you to sing.
You just used up
today's bathroom break.
Hardass.
I heard that.
Now, on your right
you'll see the slurm master
checking the slurm
for color and bouquet.
[ Slurping ]
So thirsty...
Then he tastes it.
He tastes it and tastes it,
then tastes it some more.
Uh, could I have
some slurm, please?
No food or drink
allowed on the tour.
You'll have to wait till you're
partying with slurms McKenzie.
When will that be?
Soon enough.
That's not soon enough.
Hey, what's behind that door?
Nothing.
Is it the secret
ingredient?
♪ Grunka lunka
dunkity dingredient ♪
♪ you should not ask
about the secret ingredient. ♪
Okay, okay, we get the point.
I was just curious
because of the armed guards.
♪ Grunka lunka dunkity
darmed‐guards... ♪
Shut the hell up!
So you're telling me
I could fire my whole staff
and hire grunka‐lunkas
at half the cost?
That's right.
They think they have
a good union, but they don't.
They're basically slaves.
[ Grunting ]
[ Straining ]
What are you doing?
I'm dying of thirst.
Grab my feet and dunk
my head in so I can drink.
No. That's moronic.
Fine. I'll let go
and swim around in the slurm
and drink as much as I want.
Help! I can't swim!
Oh...
[ Fry gurgling ]
[ Gasping ]
[ Hyperventilating ]
[ Whistling cheerfully ]
Bender, why did you jump in?
Everybody was doing it.
I just wanted to be popular.
[ All screaming ]
Ow!
Where are we?
And why is the slurm
pouring into this sewer?
This isn't slurm at all.
Something's rotten
on the planet wormulan.
Look at this.
[ Creatures sighing
and snoring ]
This all must have
something to do
with the secret ingredient.
My god!
What if the secret ingredient
is people?
No. There's already
a soda like that.
Soylent cola.
Oh. How is it?
It varies from person to person.
[ Cash register dinging ]
Ooh! Hmm.
[ Light music playing ]
Do you have any that aren't
so tight around the thorax?
Yes. Over in...
Say, weren't there
more people in your group
at the start of the tour?
Hey, yeah. Fry, Leela
and bender are missing.
If you'll excuse me.
[ Shrieking ]
[ All gasping ]
Quick!
[ Wormulans grumbling ]
Whoo!
Look. Slurm!
Finally.
[ Gulping ]
Oh, yeah.
I'm never going 12 minutes
without a slurm again.
It's the end of the line.
This must be where they put in
the secret ingredient.
Whatever it is,
it's even better fresh.
[ Slurping ]
Mmm. Still warm.
[ All gasping ]
[ Creature chomping ]
[ Loud splatting ]
Ohh!
Yack!
Aw! Lordy!
[ Gulping ]
Fry!
Whew!
[ Gulping ]
Fry!
That's the secret
ingredient of slurm?
That's the only
ingredient of slurm.
Eww‐hoo‐hoo!
[ Creature growling ]
Whoa!
[ Screaming ]
Aw!
[ All grunting ]
I'll save us!
Yah!
Oh, that feels good.
Yep.
Whew! Thanks, bender.
[ Clears throat ]
[ All panting ]
The exit.
We made it!
[ All gasping ]
[ Bender ]
Uh, your majesty
I brought the prisoners.
Well, my curious friends,
you learned the secret of slurm.
That concludes
the portion of the tour
where you stay alive.
You wish, you slimy worm.
Hi‐yah!
[ Creatures snickering ]
Oh!
Good work, glermo.
You have pleased your queen.
Thank you, your majesty.
Thanks, ma'am.
How can you trick people
into drinking something
that comes out of your behind?
It's disgusting.
Is it? Honey comes
from a bee's behind.
Milk comes from a cow's behind.
And have you ever used
toothpaste?
Whose behind
does that come from?
You don't want to know.
Look, we just came to party
with slurms McKenzie.
By the way,
when is that scheduled?
Never!
Oh!
To the torture cave!
[ Loudly chugging ]
You, my metal friend,
will have the honor
of becoming 174 slurm cans.
Ah, this trip
is turning into a big letdown.
As for you, you
will be submerged
in royal slurm, which,
in a matter of minutes
will transform you into
a slurm queen like myself.
But, your highness,
she's a commoner.
Her slurm will taste foul.
Yes! Which is why
we'll market it as "new slurm."
Then, when everyone hates it,
we'll bring back slurm classic
and make billions.
[ Crazed laughter ]
Oh... oh.
What about me?
You are free to go.
Yes!
If you can resist this
concentrated superslurm.
Whoa!
[ Straining ]
It's so delicious
you'll eat until you explode.
Oh, which reminds me
put a top over that sofa,
would you?
Bon appetit.
[ Muffled grunting ]
Mmm...
Farewell.
Oh. And congratulations again
on winning the contest.
[ Crazed laughter ]
Fry, untie us. Quick.
Here I come.
Let me just‐‐ one more taste.
[ Slurping ]
Mmm.
You pig.
Stop stuffing your craw
and save us.
[ Groaning ]
[ Crazed slurping and chomping ]
I can't see what's happening.
Are we boned?
Yeah, we're boned.
I can't stop eating
this delicious ooze
but I'm not going
to let you die.
[ Grunting ]
[ Slurping ]
Hurry.
[ Bender ]
What's happening?
Oh.
[ Whimpering ]
Whew!
Whoa‐ho‐ho!
Just in time.
[ Screaming ]
No!
[ Frantically grunting ]
I could fit if I didn't have
these damn arms.
[ Gnawing ]
We're close to the exit.
I can smell those filthy
orange guys.
[ Slurms McKenzie ]
Stop right there!
Slurms McKenzie!
Shh! I want you
to take me with you.
Say what?
I'm partied out.
All I want is to stay home
and rent videos
and watch them
with a few friends.
Is that so much to ask?
Forget it, pal.
It says on this bottle cap
you have to party with us.
All right, when we get to earth.
But please, don't invite
too many people.
I want to keep it small.
No can do, slurms.
[ Loud rumbling ]
[ Growling ]
[ All screaming ]
This way!
Oh! Oh!
[ Angry groaning ]
She's gaining on us.
Go on without me.
I'll hold her off.
But she'll crush you
like a worm...
Crushing a smaller worm.
It's all right.
I'm so tired of partying,
so very tired.
I'll save you
the only way
I know how. By partying!
[ Dance music playing ]
Babes?
Yes, Mr. McKenzie?
You've served me well
these 40 years, but this time,
I've got to party alone.
But...
There'll be other parties
for you.
Now go. Go.
[ Loud growling ]
♪ Yeah! Yeah! Yeah! Yeah! ♪
[ Weak growling ]
♪ Yeah! Yeah! Yeah! ♪
Party on, slurms.
Party on, contest winners.
Party on.
[ Yelps ]
[ Grunting ]
No! We're ruined!
They know our disgusting secret!
[ Bawling ]
Oh, no...!
[ Professor ]
Commissioner, my crew
has made a horrific discovery.
It seems that slurm is produced
in a colossal worm heinie.
Hmm. "Heinie," you say?
Why, with your testimony
we'll finally be able
to outlaw this insidious slurm.
Outlaw slurm?!
Uh, don't pay any attention
to him, sir.
Grandpa's making up
crazy stories again.
I'm not your grandpa.
You're my uncle.
From the year 2000!
Okay, grandpa, we'll
take care of the bad worms.
Don't you worry.
Ah, I just wish slurms McKenzie
were here to enjoy this with me.
Yeah, that slurms
sure loved to party.
What do you say we all party
one last time for him?
For slurms.
[ All ]
Whammy wozzle.
[ Dance music playing ]
[ Gulping ]
Hey, that's not that bad.
[ Loud gulping ]
Mmm!