Encoded by hunter
crazy4tv. Com
[ To the tune of "car wash" ]
♪ Goin' through the 'bot wash ♪
♪ goin' through the robot wash ♪
♪ c'mon y'all
and sing it with me ♪
♪ 'bot wash ♪
♪ whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa ♪
♪ 'bot wash, yeah ♪
Hmm?
♪ Bot wash, yeah ♪
Oh...
[ Laughing ]
[ Thunder rumbling ]
Oh!
Hey, I'm elzar.
Welcome to the show.
You know, you don't have
to drive all the way to Neptune
for great neptunian food.
Today we're going
to kick it up a notch
as I show you how to fricassee
a mouthwatering neptunian slug.
Whoo‐whee!
Now, while you're greasing
the pan
and preheating your oven
to 3,500 degrees
you're going to separate
the yolk
from your genetically enhanced
eggplant
and then give the whole thing
a good blast
from your spice weasel.
Bam!
[ Fry ]
Hey, what you watching?
Uh, nothing.
Is that a cooking show?
No, of course not.
It was, uh...
Porno.
Yeah, that's it.
Bender, I didn't know
you liked cooking.
That's so cute.
Aw, it's true.
I've been hiding it for so long.
It's okay, bender.
I like cooking, too.
Pansy.
Of course, your most
important ingredient
is this baby right here‐‐
the neptunian slug.
You can get it in a can,
but to really do things right
you got to strangle yourself
a fresh one.
[ Growling ]
Now this is why you
always want to use
cast iron cookware.
[ Jamaican accent ]
Bender, mon
it has come to my attention
that this company has been
paying you to do nothing
but loaf about on the couch.
You call that a couch?
I demand a pillow.
I'm sorry, but if you want
to continue drawing a salary
you've got to do more than watch
the cooking shows all day.
Hmm?
You're going to be
the ship's cook?
Yeah. We're going
to kick it up a notch.
Bam!
I know you like cooking shows,
but you're a robot.
You don't even have
a sense of taste.
Honey, I wouldn't talk
about taste
if was wearing
a lime green tank top.
Bam!
So this is little Neptune.
Yep. Every chef knows
this is the place
to get exotic
gourmet ingredients.
Among other things.
Come on, man!
Don't hold out on me like this!
Psst.
You want to buy organ?
Fresh and cheap
ready for transplant.
Ooh, what's this?
Ah, it's x‐ray eye.
See through anything.
Wait a minute.
This says "z‐ray."
"Z" is just as good.
In fact, it's better.
It's two more than "x."
Hmm, I can see where
that would be an advantage.
Do you take cash?
Fry, you have
to be more careful.
You're not in
the 20th century anymore.
You don't know how
things work here.
I'm not a little kid, Leela.
I grew up in this city.
These are my people.
What up?
Word.
See?
Wow! You guys sell every kind
of meat here except human.
What? You want human?
What's this spice for?
That's powdered swamp root.
Makes you irresistible
to the opposite sex.
Oh, that's ridiculous.
I'll take two pounds.
Hey, buddy
I'm looking for fresh slug.
Yellow or purple?
Whatever.
The purple one
causes terrible
nightmarish diarrhea.
Yeah, yeah, either one's fine.
Hey, have you seen fry?
Now that you mention it
I do have trouble breathing
underwater sometimes.
I'll take the gills.
Yes, gills.
Then you don't need
lungs anymore, is right?
Can't imagine why I would.
Lie down on table.
I take lungs now,
gills come next week.
Nurse!
Let's do it.
You may feel small pain.
Thank you.
What the hell were you doing?
I warned you
to stay away
from those guys.
I'm capable of making
my own decisions, Leela.
Did you ever stop to think
I might be happier with gills?
Good news, everyone.
Uh‐oh, I don't like
the sound of that.
You'll be making
a delivery to the
planet trisol.
Here it comes.
A mysterious world
in the darkest depths
of the forbidden zone.
Thank you and good night.
Uh, professor, are we even
allowed in the forbidden zone?
Why, of course.
It's just a name.
Like "the death zone"
or "the zone of no return."
All the zones have names like
that in the galaxy of terror.
Uh, professor...
Off you go.
Pleasant trip.
Hey, bender
how's dinner coming?
Almost ready.
[ Humming tune ]
Ah, now for a dash of salt.
Uh‐oh.
Listen, this is
bender's first meal
and he's a little sensitive.
So let's be supportive, okay?
Right.
Yeah, okay.
Oh, dear god!
[ All spitting ]
Ew! That's the saltiest thing
I've ever tasted.
And I once ate
a big heaping bowl of salt.
Bender, is this salt water?
That's salt with water in it,
if that's what you mean.
My vision's fading.
I think I'm going to die.
There was nothing wrong
with that food.
The salt level was ten percent
less than a lethal dose.
Uh‐oh, I shouldn't have
had seconds.
Okay, fry
here's the package to deliver.
And for once
in your life,
be careful.
This is my first visit
to the galaxy of terror
and I'd like it to
be a pleasant one.
Ow!
Don't touch anything
or talk to anyone.
Just go to the
palace, drop it off
and come right back.
Geez, will you lay off?
I was delivering things
before you were born.
I think I know what I'm doing.
[ Smacking lips ]
Oh, stupid slug.
I've never been so thirsty.
Oh, come on, go down already.
Ah.
[ Groans ]
Hello?
Anybody home?
[ Smacking lips ]
Ah!
The royal bottle is empty!
You drank our emperor!
No, it wasn't me.
[ Belches ]
[ Nervous chuckle ]
You drank our emperor!
You assassinated him!
I didn't mean to.
He just looked so cool
and refreshing.
I'm sure he was.
But now he's gone,
and your fate is sealed.
[ Loud gulp ]
All hail the new emperor!
Hail! Hail! Hail!
So after I specifically
asked you not to touch anything
you drank a bottle
of strange blue liquid.
It could have been
poisonous acid.
It could have been,
but chances were
equally good it was an emperor.
Excuse me, your majesty
I am murg, the high priest.
If I might interject?
You might.
I humbly advise
that as your first act
you choose a capable
prime minister.
I suggest gorgak,
the previous appointee.
I will be a forceful and
effective administrator.
You know, fry,
I've often thought
about becoming a prime minister.
I got to go with bender.
Yes! In your face,
gorgak!
That's it, fry.
As your captain
I order you back
to the ship.
You are in way over your head.
Gee, you think so, captain?
I'd better check
with my prime minister.
Stay the course, pal.
Your highness, a
package came for you.
Hey, thanks.
Wow, this got here just in time.
This is your majesty's harem.
You may choose any
of these maidens
to be your royal consort.
Uh, uh... how
about that one?
Oh, I didn't realize
your majesty
was into that sort of thing.
Oh second thought,
I'll take that one.
Hey, whatever you say.
I'm not here to pass judgment.
Does anyone else think it's odd
that a shiftless,
25‐year‐old delivery boy
could drop out of the sky,
kill the emperor
and be rewarded
instead of punished?
You don't have to beat
around the bush, Leela.
We all know
who you're talking about.
Me, right?
Oh, I don't think there's
anything to worry about.
These people seem
really mild‐mannered.
They are mild.
In fact, you're soaking
in one right now.
You touched me in ways
I've never been touched before.
Ah, there you are, your majesty.
It's time to begin preparing
for tomorrow's
coronation ceremony.
A fancy dress gala?
I'll wear my formal shell.
Fry will be enthroned tomorrow
at the setting of the three suns
when we trisolians
enter our nocturnal phase.
There won't be a lot
of long‐winded speeches
will there?
Only one.
The absolutely flawless
recitation from memory
of the royal oath...
By you.
Will there be cake?
[ Applause ]
And now, get ready to laugh
till your sides leak
with our planet's foremost
political satirist, florp.
[ Applause ]
So what is the deal with people
from under the orange sun?
They're all...
[ Creaking noises ]
[ Laughing ]
But us guys from under
the red sun, we're like...
[ Languid sighs ]
Right?
Am I right?
Oh, yeah, he's right.
Fry, I have to talk to you.
You're in terrible danger.
You see emperor plon here?
He met his end when he
was drunk by emperor strug.
And before he could
even wipe his mouth
strug was drunk by shwab.
So?
Look at all these guys.
Do you have any idea
what the average length
of their reigns was?
Uh... 80,000 years?
No, one week.
Damn. I knew
you wouldn't have asked
unless it was really high
or really low.
Every emperor ascended to power
by assassinating
the previous one.
And guess who's next?
Well, at least my assassin
will get what's coming to him.
You're in tremendous
danger, you idiot!
Half these emperors
were drunk at their
own coronation.
Hey, I plan on having
a few brewskis myself.
No, they were assassinated.
In fact, the law says
you'll be killed on the spot
if you fail to recite
the oath from memory.
I was going to thumb
through that later.
That is completely reckless.
Don't you ever think ahead?
Hell, no.
If I stopped to think ahead
I wouldn't be emperor
and I wouldn't even be here
in the year 3000.
It's just like the story
of the grasshopper
and the octopus.
All year long, the grasshopper
kept burying acorns for winter
while the octopus mooched
off his girlfriend
and watched TV.
But then the winter came
and the grasshopper died
and the octopus ate
all his acorns
and also he got a race car.
Is any of this getting
through to you?
I give up.
You're going to get
yourself killed
and this time I won't
be able to save you.
Who asked you to?
I told you a
hundred times
to stop treating me like a baby.
Now go.
Go gather your nuts,
you nagging grasshopper.
That's it!
I'm never helping
you again.
If anyone except you needs me
I'll be in the ship.
I'll be fine.
It's not like anyone's
going to drink me.
[ Slurping ]
Quit it.
People of trisol
it is my honor to present
your new emperor.
[ Cheering ]
[ Clearing throat ]
What up?
[ Water drips ]
Stick to the oath.
Right.
I, fry, who drank
bont the viscous
who drank ungo the moist
who guzzled zorn the stagnant
who slurped hudj the dewy
who enjoyed a soup composed
principally of throm the chunky
do solemnly swear to rule
with honor and...
Insanity...
Uh, integrity.
Congratulations, your highness.
I now present you with
your royal unisex robe.
Long live fry the solid!
[ Cheering ]
[ Bender ]
Hey, look, the
suns are setting.
I can finally switch
to hard liquor.
Ah.
Check out the glowing freaks.
It's beautiful.
Hey, what's that?
[ Gasping ]
The emperor bont!
He's still alive!
Of course I'm alive.
Now cut this creep open
and drain me out.
My tummy hurts.
[ Bont ]
They're over here.
They're running up the stairs.
Shut up, you.
[ Groans ]
[ Murg ]
Let us in!
Fry must die
so that bont may live.
What am I going to do?
We've got to get
the emperor out
of your body
before they kill you.
Relax, fry.
I'll simply spin you
in a high‐speed centrifuge
separating out the denser
fluid of his highness.
But won't that crush my bones?
Oh, right, right,
with the bones.
I always forget about the bones.
Hey, why don't you just
sweat him out?
Forget it.
As emperor, I refuse
to be dripped out
through somebody's armpit.
I could vomit or urinate.
Would you feel better
about that?
Slightly.
But my favorite so far
is the bone crushing.
What about crying?
That's a great idea.
Crying.
Fine.
That or the bone one.
Keep it up, men.
The veneer is starting to peel.
Oh, dear.
It's no use.
I want to cry,
but I'm just too macho.
I'll make you cry, buddy.
You're a pimple on society's ass
and you'll never
amount to anything.
What do you mean?
I was emperor of a whole planet.
Good point.
But here's a
disturbing reminder:
Everyone you knew or loved
in the 20th century is dead.
These things happen.
Okay, fry, grab a
kleenex for this one
'cause there's no god
and your idiotic human ideals
are laughable.
[ Laughing ]
Whew.
That's a load off my mind.
Man, I guess it's
harder than I thought
to make someone cry.
You did your best, bender.
Up yours, bimbo!
[ Sobbing ]
Let's face it,
we're in hot butter here.
We should call Leela for help.
Cram it, lobster.
[ Zoidberg crying ]
But that is a good idea.
I'll go call her.
Aw, she'll never help me.
She's still mad that I told her
never to help me.
Come on, Leela's
not the type to hold a grudge.
[ Phone ringing ]
[ Female voice ]
Collect call from...
[ Bender ]
I'm not giving my name
to a machine!
I'll accept.
Fry's in trouble
and he needs help.
Now, I don't like you
and you don't like me.
I like you.
You do?
Look, are you going
to help or not?!
I don't know why I should.
I mean, after what he...
Wait. Wait.
What is it you like
best about me?
Is she coming?
I'm not sure, but I do know
that she likes my
in‐your‐face attitude.
[ Rumbling ]
What the hell is that?!
It's the juice‐ a‐matic 4000.
It'll strain my juices from you
while filtering out the pulp.
By which I mean
your shredded remains.
Of course.
Why didn't I think of that?
This is the saddest day
of my life...
And I still can't cry.
[ Splashing ]
Wait a second.
Here comes Leela!
They have her
totally outnumbered.
I can't believe it.
She's risking her life for me
after the way I treated her?
Oh...
I don't deserve this.
I feel terrible.
You do?
Hmm...
Is she all right?
I don't know.
Perhaps I'll look
out this window.
Oh, dear god in heaven!
They're swarming all over her!
No! No!
What are you talking
about, bender?
She's...
[ Muffled speech ]
There's strapping her
to the juicer!
Oh, they're
putting some
ice cubes
in the glass under it.
[ Moans desperately ]
This can't be happening!
It can, and for all
you know, it is.
I'm sorry, fry.
She's dead.
[ Crying ]
All Leela ever wanted to do
was help me
and I was too proud
and stupid to accept it.
I wish I had died
instead of her.
[ Leela ]
What are you
talking about?
Leela!
You're alive!
Of course I'm alive.
I told fry you were dead
so he would cry out the emperor
but you had to go
and wreck it by surviving.
We only got two drops.
[ Bursting ]
[ Cackling ]
It's only a matter of time now.
I'll handle this.
Listen, fry, I think
I can get us out of this
if you're willing
to let me help you.
Thanks, Leela.
From now on, I'll
take all the help
you're willing to give.
I know you just want
what's best for me.
Ow!
What was that for?!
Hey, come on!
That hurt!
I know.
Amy, get the bottle.
Ow!
[ Sniveling ]
Oh, now I understand.
Come on. Everybody
help out fry.
Ow! Ow!
Ow!
[ Crying ]
Thanks, everybody.
I love you all.
You guys are true...
Oh!
Cut it out, bender.
That's a tender area.
How we doing, Amy?
Great. We're one‐tenth
of the way there.
[ Crying ]
[ Punching sounds ]
[ Panting ]
Okay, it's your turn.
Hey, wait a minute.
Who are you?
I'm the emperor.
Thanks for crying me out.
Oh, you're welcome.
Oh!
[ Continues grunting in pain ]
[ Bender ]
Hey, save some for me!