Encoded by hunter
crazy4tv. Com
[ professor ]
Good news, everyone.
Tomorrow,
you'll be making a delivery
to ebola 9, the virus planet.
Why can't they go today?
Because tonight's
a special night
and I want all of you
to be alive.
It's the academy of inventors
annual symposium.
Wow, I love symposia.
It's the event
of the scientific season.
Every member presents
an invention
and the best one
wins the academy prize.
Sounds boring.
Oh, my, yes, but not this year
because my latest
invention is unbeatable.
Behold...
The death clock.
Simply jam your
finger in the hole
and this readout tells you
exactly how long you
have left to live.
Does it really work?
Well, it's occasionally
off by a few seconds
what with free will and all.
Sounds like fun.
How long do I have to live?
[ Bell dings ]
[ Whistles ]
Ooh, dibs on his cd player!
[ Chattering ]
Who's the gross nerd?
That's me,
at the very first symposium.
I'm the academy's
oldest living member, you know.
These youngsters
all look up to me.
[ Man ]
Well, well, well...
Look who decided
to show his wrinkled face.
Why don't you
just leave me alone, wernstrom?
Face it, Farnsworth,
you're over the hill.
It's time to leave science
to the 120‐year‐olds.
You young turks think
you know everything.
I was inventing things
when you were barely
turning senile.
[ Laughs ]
Go home before you embarrass
yourself, old man.
Now, if you'll excuse me
I'm going to take a nap
before the ceremonies.
Who's that jerk?
A hundred years ago
he was my most promising
student at Mars university
but then,
after one fateful pop quiz...
"A‐minus"?
No one gives ogden wernstrom
an a‐minus.
I'm sorry,
but penmanship counts.
I swear I'll have my revenge
if it takes me a hundred years.
And here it is
slightly over 99 years later
and still no revenge.
I'm essentially in the clear.
[ Chattering ]
I've been perusing
your fortified wine list
and I've selected
the '71 hobo's delight,
the '57 chateau part‐ay and
the '66 thunder‐schewitz.
Exquisite choices, sir.
And mix them all together
in a big jug.
Welcome to this year's
academy symposium.
I'm your host, Ron popeil‐‐
inventor of Mr. Microphone,
the spray‐on toupee
and, of course, the technology
to keep human heads alive
in jars.
But wait, there's more!
We've got a whole lineup
of inventors tonight
starting with
that up‐and‐coming young star
ogden wernstrom.
Boo!
More wine!
Distinguished members
of the academy
I present to you
the reverse scuba suit.
Observe.
Fetch.
[ Thud ]
[ Sloshing ]
Now sit.
I said, "sit."
Bad fish!
[ Applause ]
Oh.
Don't worry, professor.
It's no competition
for your death clock.
And what will you be presenting
this evening, grandpa?
Let's just say
it'll put you young
whippersnappers
in your place.
I just hope it's not as lame
as that death clock
you presented last year.
Eh, "last year," you say?
That's right.
Oh, my.
Did it put you young
whippersnappers
in your place?
Hardly.
We laughed
until our teeth fell out.
Come along, cinnamon.
Oh, dear.
I'll have
to invent something new
in the next ten minutes‐‐
perhaps some sort
of death clock.
Uh, professor?
[ Jet engine revving ]
[ Chopper blades whirring ]
[ Murmuring ]
Our last presentation comes
from our oldest member‐‐
professor Hubert Farnsworth.
Professor?
[ Stammering ]
Just a second.
Pencils down, prune face.
[ Grumbles ]
Oh, yes, here I am.
Okay, now. Hello there.
Now, we all know telescopes
allow us to see distant objects
but what if we want
to smell distant objects?
Well, now we can,
thanks to my new invention‐‐
the smelloscope.
[ Excited murmuring ]
The odor travels past
this coffee stain here
around the olive pit and
into this cigar burn...
And this appears to be a‐a...
Doodle of myself as a cowboy.
[ Laughing ]
But the smelloscope
is brilliant, I tell you!
Think of the astronomical odors
you'll smell, thanks to me!
[ Jeering laughter ]
Oh, my.
[ Laughing ]
I've waited a hundred years
for this, Farnsworth.
I give your invention
the worst grade imaginable‐‐
an a‐minus‐minus!
[ Laughing ]
And now for the presentation
of the award.
Listen, folks
I'm practically giving
this prize away
to Dr. Wernstrom
for his fish thingy.
[ Applause ]
[ Sniffles ]
Oh.
Perhaps 149 is just too
old to be a scientist.
Yep.
No, professor.
Don't give up.
There were plenty of times
in my century
when I was going to give up,
but I never did. Never.
Hey, are you even
listening to me?
Oh, I give up.
By god, you're right!
I'm going to build
that smelloscope.
[ Professor ]
Eureka!
Did you build the smelloscope?
No. I remembered
that I built one last year.
Go ahead, try it.
You'll find
that every heavenly body has
its own particular scent.
Here, I'll point it at Jupiter.
[ Grinding ]
[ Sniffing ]
Smells like strawberries.
Exactly.
And now saturn.
[ Sniffing ]
Pine needles.
Oh, man, this is great.
As long as you don't make me
smell uranus.
[ Laughing ]
I don't get it.
I'm sorry, fry
but astronomers
renamed uranus in 2620
to end that stupid joke
once and for all.
Oh. What's it called now?
Urectum.
Here, let me locate it for you.
How about‐‐ [ Laughs ]
No, no, I think I'll
just smell around
a bit over here.
[ Sniffing ]
Hmm.
[ Retching ]
What is it?
[ Sniffing ]
Oh, jeez, oh, man!
Remarkable!
A stench so foul,
it's right off the funk‐ometer.
I daresay,
fry may have discovered
the smelliest object
in the known universe.
Ooh! Ooh!
Name it after me!
[ Sniffing ]
I think it's moving.
Hmm. Perhaps the computer
can calculate its trajectory.
My god!
Whatever it is,
it's headed straight for us
with enough force
to reduce this entire city
to a stinky crater!
We have less than 72 hours.
[ All gasping ]
Well, let's get looting.
[ Whistling ]
So this thing's going
to destroy the whole city?
What the heck is it?
Ah, just as I thought.
The answer lies in this movie
I found on the Internet.
[ Dramatic music playing ]
[ Man ]
New York City: The year 2000.
The most wasteful society
in the history of the galaxy
and it was running out of places
to Bury its never‐ending
output of garbage.
The landfills were full.
New Jersey was full.
And so, under cover of darkness
the city put its garbage
out to sea
on the world's largest barge.
[ Whistling tune ]
The repulsive barge circled
the oceans for 50 years
but no country would accept it‐‐
not even that really filthy one.
You know the one I mean.
Finally, in 2052, the city
used its mob connections
to obtain a rocket
and launch the garbage
into outer space.
Some experts claim the ball
might return to earth someday
but their concerns
were dismissed
as depressing.
Wow, you got that
off the Internet?
In my day, the Internet
was only used
to download pornography.
Actually, that's still true.
Now that the garbage
is in space, doctor
perhaps you can help me
with my sexual inhibitions.
With gusto.
Aw.
So that's the situation.
Due to the shortsightedness
of old New York
new New York is going
to be destroyed
by a giant ball of garbage.
Fry, what the hell
were you people
thinking back then?
How could you just
throw your garbage away?
Hey, hey, give me a break.
What do you do with it?
We recycle everything.
Robots are made
from old beer cans.
Yeah, and this beer can
is made out of old robots.
And that sandwich you're eating
is made from old
discarded sandwiches.
Nothing just gets thrown away.
The future is disgusting.
Typical 20th‐century attitude.
Hey, you have no right
to criticize the 20th century.
We gave the world
the light bulb, the steamboat
and the cotton gin.
Those things are all
from the 19th century.
Yeah, well,
they probably
just copied us.
Please, there's no time
for this now.
This is an emergency.
We must warn the mayor.
[ Man ]
Garbage ball, huh?
That sounds serious.
Very serious, mayor poopenmeyer.
I got be sure this isn't
another scientific fraud
like global warming
or secondhand smoke.
Send in my science advisor.
Wernstrom!
Well, well, well.
Come to present your latest
napkin, professor?
No, I'm here because
a giant trash ball
is heading straight for us.
Smell for yourself.
[ Sniffs ]
Holy‐‐ gee!
That smell could be anything‐‐
a faulty stench coil, some
cheese on the lens, who knows?
Mr. Mayor, we just got this
transmission from Neptune.
[ Man gagging ]
Giant garbage ball...
Passed close by.
Horrible stench!
[ Gagging ]
The transmission
cuts out there, sir.
[ Gagging continues ]
No, I guess it keeps going.
[ Gagging and retching ]
There we go.
My god!
The senile old man is right!
Do you mean him or me?
Him.
Oh.
Next: New New York in crisis.
Morbo?
Thanks, human female.
Puny earthlings
were shocked today
to learn that a ball of garbage
will destroy
their pathetic city
of new New York.
Makes me glad we live
here in Los Angeles.
Morbo agrees.
[ Both laughing ]
[ Leela ]
Can't we just
shoot a missile at it?
We've simulated that
on a supercomputer
but the ball is just
too damn gooey.
A missile would go
right through it.
[ Squishing ]
But suppose we sent a crew
to plant an explosive
precisely on the fault line
between this mass
of coffee grounds
and this deposit
of America online floppy disks.
In theory, it could work.
Uh, in theory, perhaps
but you'll never find a crew
willing to take on a mission
so suicidally dangerous.
Aw, crap.
[ Farnsworth ]
Now you'll only have
one chance
to destroy the ball.
After that
it will be so close to earth
that blowing it up
would cause garbage to rain
over the entire planet
killing billions.
Aw, boo‐hoo.
Now here's the bomb
I've prepared.
Once you activate it
you'll have 25 minutes
to get away.
That's all? But‐‐
now, now.
There'll be plenty of time
to discuss your objections
when and if you return.
Odor at magnitude eight.
[ All gagging ]
Magnitude 12.
[ Gagging and retching ]
Magnitude 31.
We're breaking up.
Turn on the anti‐smell device.
[ Hissing ]
[ Fry ]
Hmm, sporty.
[ Squishing ]
Wow!
[ Leela ]
Look at all this filth.
[ Fry ]
It's not filth.
It's a glorious monument
to the achievements
of the 20th century.
Look, a real beanie baby.
Oh, a Mr. Spock
collectors' plate.
[ Gasps ]
Some Bart Simpson dolls.
Eat my shorts.
Okay.
Mmm, shorts.
Fry, this stuff
was garbage when
it was new.
Let's blow it up already.
This junk isn't garbage.
I can dig in any random pile
and find something great.
[ Choking ]
[ Gasping ]
All right, let's get to work.
Let's see.
If that's hypodermic Ridge
then the bomb must go
right here.
Get ready to run.
We've got 25 minutes.
Uh, 15 minutes.
Five minutes.
Six‐h minutes?
Hmm.
There's your problem.
The professor put
the counter on upside down.
That idiot.
It wasn't set for 25 minutes.
It was set for 52 seconds.
[ Screaming ]
We're going to die!
Right?
Right.
[ Screaming ]
It's going to blow!
[ Panicked yelping ]
Hey, watch it!
You'll put somebody's eye out!
Okay, okay,
keep your space pants on.
I'll take care of this.
[ Sputtering ]
[ Relieved sighs ]
We're saved.
Yeah, but this garbage ball's
unstoppable now.
New New York is done for.
[ Jeering ]
All in all, this is one day
mittens the kitten
won't soon forget.
[ Chuckling ]
Kittens give morbo gas.
In lighter news
the city of new New York is
doomed.
Blame rests with known human
professor Hubert Farnsworth
and his tiny inferior brain.
Oh, how could I have put
that bomb timer on upside down?
I could swear I followed
the manual precisely.
I'm a dried‐up husk
of a scientist.
This is all my fault.
No, it's my fault, too.
I'm sure I threw out
more than my share
of that trash up there.
Also, one month, my toilet broke
and I just went
straight in the garbage can.
Aw!
Leela was right.
The people of
the 20th century
were idiotic slobs.
Especially me.
Enough. You all
failed miserably.
It's time to put
a real scientist in charge.
Wernstrom!
The very same.
Dr. Wernstrom, can
you save my city?
Of course, but it'll cost you.
First, I'll need tenure.
Done.
And a big research Grant.
You got it.
Also access to a lab
and five graduate students‐‐
at least three of them Chinese.
All right, done.
What's your plan?
What plan?
I'm set for life.
Au revoir, suckers.
That rat.
Do something.
I wish I could,
but he's got tenure.
[ All sniffing ]
[ All ]
Eww!
[ Screaming ]
[ Slurping ]
It's time to take action.
Stephanie,
cancel the maid for today.
Have her come tomorrow.
Well, I'm out of ideas.
Anyone?
Wait.
If we could build an object
the exact size, density
and consistency
of the garbage ball
it might just knock
the ball away
without smashing it to bits.
But where can we
find a substance
the exact density and
consistency as garbage?
Alas, I don't know.
Uh, what about garbage?
Good lord!
A second ball of garbage.
That just might work.
But garbage isn't something
you just find lying
in the streets of Manhattan.
This city's been garbage‐free
for 500 years.
Well, then it's time
to make some more.
Make garbage?
But how?
Stand back and watch the master.
This slurm can‐‐
now it's garbage.
These papers‐‐
garbage.
This picture of your wife‐‐
pure garbage.
Now you try it.
By god, I think
the boy's got something.
Come on, everyone.
The fate of the city's at stake.
Good.
Don't finish that cruller.
Throw it away.
Bender, drink that beer
and drop the bottle
on the ground.
Very nice.
Get that robot some more beer.
Hmm?
We've trashed this room
but that's just a start.
We've got to get fry's
message to the people.
People of new New York
take a lesson
from the 20th century‐‐
stop all this
pain‐in‐the‐ass recycling
and throw your garbage
on the floor.
Go ahead, just Chuck it
any old place like I used to.
Your city is counting on you.
[ Farnsworth ]
If my calculations are correct
this garbage ball will knock
the other garbage ball
directly into the sun.
And if my
calculations
are correct
we're all going to die horribly.
[ Laughing ]
[ Laughter subsides ]
All right, places, everyone.
Prepare for launch.
Five, four, three, two,
three, four, five, six‐‐
just fire the damn thing.
[ Fry ]
Oops.
[ Heart beating ]
‐ [ One heartbeat ]
‐ [ Drum beating ]
[ Sniffing ]
Burning garbage.
It worked!
[ Cheering ]
And so, on behalf
of the entire city
I thank you,
professor Farnsworth.
I now present you
with the academy prize
which we confiscated
from Dr. Wernstrom
after it became apparent
that he was a jackass.
[ Applause ]
Yes! In your face,
wernstrom!
I'll get you, Farnsworth
even if it takes another
hundred years.
[ Angry grunts ]
And, fry, we owe you
a tremendous debt as well.
Were it not for
your 20th‐century
garbage‐making skills
we'd all be buried
under 20th‐century garbage.
[ Applause ]
Should we really be celebrating?
I mean, what if
this second garbage ball
returns to earth
like the first one did?
Well, who cares?
That won't be for
hundreds of years.
Exactly. It's none
of our concern.
That's the 20th‐ century spirit.
[ Cheering ]
♪ We'll meet again ♪
♪ don't know where ♪
♪ I don't know when ♪
♪ but I know
we'll meet again ♪
♪ some sunny day ♪
♪ oh, keep smiling through ♪